What's the matter?
Uh... Something in my ear.
Can you hear me, Yuji Itadori?
Listen and—
Wait, wait, wait! I'm your ally, you idiot!
It's me, Mechamaru from the Kyoto school!
There's no time.
Listen and understand the first time.
Satoru Gojo has been sealed.
Goodnight, Satoru Gojo.
We'll meet again in the new world.
Maybe for me.
But it's time for you to wake up already.
How long will you keep letting it have its way with you, Suguru?
Incredible!
This is a first!
Hey, Geto.
Mahito, look at this.
You proposed that the soul exists before the body,
but actually, the body is part of the soul,
and the soul is part of the body.
There's no other way to explain this phenomenon
or the fact that the body's memories flow into my brain after I swap hosts.
Does that really have to be a universal truth?
Are you sure the world doesn't operate differently for your technique and mine?
So each technique is its own world-view?
I like it. What a lovely idea.
Hey!
If you're going to do this, hurry it up.
Not only is it absolutely foul, but the view here is awful, too.
I wanted to enjoy this sight for a bit longer, but...
Indeed, I wouldn't want anything to happen.
Gate, Close.
Now we can't use this anymore, right?
Yeah, it only holds one.
Unless the man inside kills himself, it's unusable now.
Huh. Lame.
Well, in any case...
The sealing is complete.
We're talking about Satoru Gojo here.
What proof do you have for me to believe you?
Sorry, but I have nothing.
If I must provide something,
it's the very fact that I'm here.
I was killed on October 19th
by the special-grade cursed spirit called Mahito.
What's here is now is no more than the insurance I left when I was still alive.
Advanced insurance, yes.
So I had no choice but to
set its condition for activating to "after Satoru Gojo has been sealed."
To decrease the risk of it not going off,
I only managed to sneak these puppets into three locations ahead of time.
Yuji Itadori was the Jujutsu Tech sorcerer
least likely to be leaking any information.
And Mei Mei, given the situation, I'm now certain you're in the clear, too.
Why?
Because someone as skilled at intelligence gathering as you
was dispatched here to Meiji Shrine Station instead of acting in the shadows at Shibuya.
Itadori wasn't even a part of Jujutsu society until several months ago, either.
Hey, that might have been so I'd have an excuse to refuse aiding them.
Besides, I'm the one who has kept stopping Itadori
from heading straight to Shibuya all this time.
Even if we were ordered to be on standby.
Then why...
is a curse user currently heading your way to eliminate you?
One, two... Two, huh?
Itadori, which is stronger, these two or the cursed spirit you fought earlier?
They're probably stronger than that grasshopper.
Apparently, the cursed spirit Itadori fought was able to speak human language,
so it was semi-first-grade or higher, at least...
and things like that are crawling out of the woodwork?
I wonder where they've been hiding and what they've been up to until now.
Let's ignore the curse users and move onward.
We need to confirm Gojo's status first.
Don't.
The situation in Shibuya has already changed.
Their barrier techniques are several degrees better than ours.
There are currently four Veils lowered over Shibuya,
A: the Veil trapping common people inside,
B: the Veil trapping Satoru Gojo inside,
C: the Veil keeping sorcerers from entering,
and D: another Veil like A to keep common people trapped inside.
And you're saying the area further down these tracks is blocked by C.
That's right.
The sorcerers on standby are already inside the Veil, right?
And you can't use cell phones inside the Veil.
Looks like that's not all, either.
I can't get a hold of the assistant supervisors who are supposed to be outside the Veils.
Please, just follow my directions.
This insurance of mine won't last long.
Please.
Mei.
All right, tell us.
Itadori, return to Meiji Shrine Station, and head to Shibuya from the surface.
Tell all the sorcerers there about Gojo being sealed.
Get them to share our goal of recovering Gojo.
Right!
Mei Mei, create an opportunity for Itadori to escape.
After defeating the curse users,
I'd like you to follow this track, for starters.
But I don't know what moves the enemy will make.
So adapt and respond.
By the way, they haven't frozen your bank account yet, have they?
Huh?
If Satoru Gojo disappears, both jujutsu and human society will be upended.
I'm sorry, but please stake your life on this.
And I even thought that would be worth it once...
I was the worst.
Hey, what about me?
Follow whichever one you prefer.
Okay, Nee-sama it is!
Everyone, they're here.
You're Mei Mei, right?
Go ahead and do as you please.
I'll match you.
Thanks!
Looks like you're all awake.
Now, for our next...
What's wrong?
I can't believe this guy!
Looks like physical time isn't passing inside here.
Man, I screwed up.
This is all kinds of bad.
Well, it'll all work out somehow.
I'm counting on you, everyone.
True...
Even accounting for those trapped inside the station,
the crowd density was low.
So the transfigured humans were lying in wait inside the buildings,
and now they've started attacking the non-sorcerers, huh?
That's why we've stopped standing by and started to act.
There wasn't much else we could do.
Our response is falling too far behind.
But my biggest concern is...
The Veil—
The Veil keeping sorcerers out that lowered at the same time, right?
It's been some time since Gojo arrived at the site.
Why did they choose now, of all times?
Either something has happened inside
or they needed to wait for this moment as part of their strategy.
All I can say for certain is
that these aren't the types to face us without a plan.
I'll focus on the enemies who lowered the Veils.
You two, please rescue all the common people you can.
Yes. Right.
Once you've confirmed the situation, please exit the Veil again, Nitta.
With signal blocked inside,
we'll constantly need someone on the outside.
I would like you to take on that role.
We'll do whatever it takes
to establish a communication network using just the assistant supervisors.
It should be possible if we mobilize those off-duty
and a portion of our windo—
Yah!
Man, bullying the weak really is the best job for me!
This is what you all want, right?
Yes.
Please continue hunting down all the humans in suits outside the Veil.
Okay!
And I can go inside once I'm finished, right?
What's this? What's going on?
The sealing is complete.
However, the Prison Realm still hasn't finished processing
all of the information that is Satoru Gojo.
We won't be able to move it for a while.
They got one over on us.
Itadori, good news!
Huh?
They can't move Gojo from where he was sealed on floor B5.
Why not?!
Because he's Satoru Gojo.
Makes sense!
Let's encircle them.
We'll have sorcerers follow the subway lines
into Shibuya Station from each neighboring station.
Then, once the Veil keeping sorcerers out is lifted, we charge in.
Have them follow them? But I can't get a hold of Ijichi!
Oh...
What?!
Hey, who was sent to Shibuya?
Well...
Kill me.
D-D-D-Did you call for me?
Nanamin!
Nanamin, are you here?!
Itadori?
N-Nanamin?
Gojo...
has been sealed!
...has been sealed!
Sealed?!
You two, change of plans.
We meet up with Itadori at once.
If it's true that he's been sealed,
then it's over.
For every human in this country.
Man, now they know what we're doing.
The sorcerers are going to come here in force now.
I'll be staying behind. What about the rest of you?
I'm getting revenge for my younger brothers,
and killing Yuji Itadori and Nobara Kugisaki.
Then I'll go get the rest of my brothers from where they're being kept in Jujutsu Tech.
I don't care about this Kugisaki, but you can't kill Itadori.
We're turning him into Sukuna.
Not my problem.
Jogo, calm down.
Honestly, I think I want to kill Itadori, too.
Mahito! What are you—
From what I could tell after seeing Satoru Gojo in person,
now that he's sealed away, the sorcerers and cursed spirits are evenly matched.
If Sukuna is resurrected, we'll have a huge advantage,
and victory is basically ours, right?
Well, that's true.
But then,
that also means we're perfectly capable of winning with the forces we have now, right?
So let's kill Itadori!
It'll be fine!
Even if we lose Sukuna, we can still win.
Are you serious?
As serious as can be.
I don't need to be the one smiling in the wasteland a century from now.
As long as curses can live as people, that's all that matters.
Sukuna isn't our ally.
We might even be the ones facing greater risk if he is resurrected.
But if Sukuna is resurrected, that's guaranteed to usher in the age of curses.
We are not like the humans of today.
We do not fear death,
and we follow the path to our goals without falsehoods.
That is the essence of us curses that those fakes lack.
You're wrong.
Wha?!
No matter how off-kilter or inconsistent,
we always act in accordance with our true desires.
That's what it means to be a curse.
Oh, when I said you were wrong, I meant regarding what curses are.
I agree, the whole resurrection thing is one possibility.
Nor do I really want to fight you over it.
So how about we play a game?
If I run into Itadori first, I'll kill him.
If you find him first, you can give him the fingers and let Sukuna regain his power.
And if I find him first, I kill him. That okay?
Hey!
Oh! You want in, too, Choso?
That's fine, of course.
You're more on Jogo's side if you had to pick, right, Geto?
What about you?
I have to stay here and watch over the Prison Realm.
So I'll abstain.
Do whatever you'd like.
As far as I'm concerned,
Sukuna was just the alternative if the Prison Realm failed.
This is ridiculous.
All the sorcerers, even Itadori, will be heading this way to save Gojo.
So all you have to do is wait here.
This won't even be a game.
Ready, go!
Wha—Wait up!
Those cursed spirits are smarter than you two.
Give him back.
We cooperated with you and kept dropping monkeys for you.
Now give us back Geto-sama's body like you promised.
Don't toy with...
...Geto-sama any further.
Obviously, I'm not giving him back.
I don't recall leaving your heads empty, too.
Next time you make a promise with a sorcerer,
you should make it clear that it's a pact.
Now, begone.
Or do you want to be killed by this body?
You'll regret this.
Regret, huh?
Now...
How did that taste again?
Nanamin!
Na-na-min! Na-na-min!
Na-na-na-na-na-na-min!
Hey.
Hey!
Na-na—
Fushiguro! Nanamin!
And... who?
You really were referring to Nanami with that "Nanamin," huh?
Geto did?
To be more precise, the thing that's living within Suguru Geto.
The inside of Shibuya Station is currently a real Pandemonium.
It's full of those special-grades, the cursed spirits they brought with them,
the curse users tied to Geto,
as well as transfigured humans and normal people.
In that case, it would be faster to attack through
the subway from the neighboring stations.
But in order to do that, we need to lift that Veil first.
It's an emergency.
Please multi-task.
I guess this isn't the time for complaining.
There are several requests only a first-grade can fulfill.
I'll step outside and take care of all those with Ijichi.
During that time, I want you three to do something
about the Veil keeping sorcerers out.
Ino.
Kusakabe and Zenin's special first-grade
sorcerer should be inside this Veil, as well.
If you're able to meet up with them,
please tell them about the situation and request their help.
I think they already understand the situation, though, thanks to that shouting.
Roger that!
Also, please take care of these two.
I will!
Ino?
Nanami is counting on me!
You two!
Before we start the mission, let me make it clear how important this is.
The two main issues with losing Gojo...
First, the collapse of the Gojo clan.
The Gojo clan is currently a one-man team of Satoru Gojo himself.
There are also lots of sorcerers who have been saved
due to Gojo's influence, pride, and whims.
Itadori, you're one of those sorcerers, right?
Yeah!
So casual about it!
All of those people are going to find themselves in trouble,
and, worst case, eliminated!
That brings us to issue two: the collapse of the power balance.
All of the cursed spirits and curse users who've
been keeping quiet because Satoru Gojo was around
will start taking action all at once.
Now, if those guys from issue two try starting a war
while society's in disarray from fighting over issue one,
we'll lose.
That's the future as Nanami and I see it.
So what do you think happens if we lose?
At the very least, the age of humans would probably be over for Japan.
See, you get it!
Now, let's go, you guys!
We'll break that Veil before Nanami gets back!
Let's rescue Satoru Gojo!
Did you hear that, Awasaka?
"Satoru Gojo has been sealed."
They're leaking information to their enemies.
What's wrong with that, Old Ogami?
It's finally starting to feel real to me.
Satoru Gojo really has been sealed.
I'm getting excited.
I wonder what's going to happen to this country now.
Nothing new.
People will curse, be cursed, and die.
Madam, did you hear?
They said the Gojos' little Satoru was sealed!
Oh, my!
I always thought that would happen to that boy one day!
He was always flaunting his style,
acting like he was nothing but leg below his nipples!
Next time, "Seance"!
Oh, Geto, did you hear? The Gojos' little—