There's so many of them!
I can't just ignore them!
But I don't have time to save everyone!
Dammit! What do I do?!
The station... Mr. Gojo... is so close!
Pollack roe!
I know those words!
Inumaki!
Salmon!
I'll leave you to it!
Salmon, salmon.
Don't move!
Itadori Yuji!
I'll avenge my brothers!
Convergence!
Blood Manipulation: Convergence.
By applying pressure on blood,
it is compressed to its limit.
The compressed blood is then released
through a single point.
When enhanced with cursed energy,
its initial speed well exceeds the speed of sound.
This name of this Blood Manipulation technique is
Piercing Blood.
Double impact? What an odd technique.
There's something I have to ask you.
Did my little brothers leave any last words?
Brothers?
I'm talking about the two you killed.
No, they didn't.
But...
They did cry.
Eso! Kechizu!
Watch me.
Watch your older brother!
Damn it.
He got distance on me again.
That beam of blood is too fast.
Chances of dodging it are fifty-fifty.
If I make the wrong guess and take one to the head...
I'm dead.
Then at the very least...
I get to decide when he fires his shot.
Trying to get me to attack?
I'll play along.
I knew it!
That attack only starts off fast.
Once I dodge it, I can get in close!
Supernova.
Tch.
I got hasty.
It wasn't compressed enough.
This bastard...
He's strong!
Hey!
What's the situation now?
Mechamaru! What have you been—
Conserving energy.
There are things I have yet to do.
Choso! Is that Blood Manipulation?
You know it?
Kamo uses the same technique.
That third-year with the narrow eyes?
Does that mean...
I don't know its weakness.
Geh!
Blood Manipulation is treasured as one of the Kamo clan's hereditary techniques.
It's because the blood compressed with Convergence
can be used for Piercing Blood and Blood Blade,
making it extremely well-balanced at any range.
It's perfect for Choso
since he won't bleed out.
Thanks for the critical info—
I don't know its weakness, but I do have an idea.
What is it?
Start with fleeing into the restroom.
The restroom?! Why?!
I'll explain later.
There's maybe a ten percent chance of success.
I apologize in advance in case it fails
and you end up dead.
Not cool!
Or you can continue to
drag this out until you're killed.
What an idiot.
That only leads to the restrooms and the elevator.
No matter which you run to, you're trapped like a rat.
What's that sound?
This guy defeated my brothers.
Those two wouldn't lose to some idiot.
And what's the deal with that other voice?
Something's going on. I bettter stay on my toes.
What's wrong? Getting cold feet?
You are such a coward.
Just like your brothers.
Now you've done it.
You really are just like them.
You three care so much for each other.
Makes you easy to manipulate.
It's all gone well so far.
Now it's a gamble, Itadori Yuji!
What a pity.
That was your last chance.
You've got nowhere to run now!
Convergence was dispelled?!
In order to use Blood Manipulation effectively,
the user halts the coagulation properties of their blood.
As a result, Choso's blood dissolves in water
more easily than normal blood.
Additionally, the osmotic pressure causes the
red blood cells to expand and rupture their membranes.
Unable to control the blood cells that make up
close to forty-five percent of his blood,
Convergence was dispelled.
Mechamaru's intuition was correct.
As things stand, Choso can no longer control
the blood outside his body.
Flowing Red Scale: Stack.
Choso lacked combat experience, so he couldn't
comprehend what was happening to him.
He simply accepted the new reality and
focused on manipulating blood inside his body.
I'm not sure what's going on.
Never got the chance to ask for an explanation.
All I know is...
I've dragged him into my turf!
I can win!
The moment he was convinced of victory,
coagulated and compressed to the extreme
and reinforced with cursed energy,
the clot of blood kept hidden from water
shot through Itadori Yuji's liver.
Blood Manipulation: Blood Meteorite.
I screwed up! I assumed he couldn't use any projectiles!
Wait... Where did I get hit?
This is different from when I had that hole in my gut!
It broke something that shouldn't be broken!
I'm gonna lose...
and die!
I understand what my role is.
I'll take this guy out even if it kills me.
I don't have to be the one to rescue Mr. Gojo.
Three hits.
In just three hits, excluding the ones I blocked,
he managed to deal this much damage to me...
Blood Meteorite's only strength is its hardness.
It doesn't have the speed or impact of Piercing Blood.
It wouldn't have worked if I hadn't caught him by surprise.
Blood Manipulation usually isn't used
to coagulate blood like with Blood Meteorite.
Blood Blade solidifies only the edges and circulates
the rest at high speeds for heightened lethality.
Even sorcerers who use Blood Manipulation
can't concentrate on every blood vessel at once.
Coagulating their blood always poses the risk
of spontaneous thrombosis.
Bring it.
However, Choso decided the risk
posed by Itadori Yuji was far greater.
Too strong!
Is that a tooth?!
It was a distraction!
Not yet!
I haven't used my left fist since that first punch.
I bet he thinks I can't use it anymore.
Wait, that didn't feel right.
Too bad.
He's still breathing.
When you're on the other side,
make sure you apologize to my brothers!
What a waste.
Losing to some nobody.
What?
In that moment, Choso's mind was
flooded with memories.
Memories that never happened.
Come on!
Have a bite, Brother!
What...
You're...
There he is.
He's alive, right?
Yeah.
Let's get this started, then.
Moan-day?
Monday.
Tuesday!
Correct!
Weh-do-ness-day?
Wednesday.
Screw this!
Next time, Fluctuations.
Who the hell came up with these readings?!
Someone smarter than you, dummy.