Yuji.
Hmm?
You're a strong kid, so help others.
In my Ten Shadows Technique,
only two Demon Dogs are granted to the user at first.
The other shikigami aren't granted to the user until they finish subjugating them.
The user must continue subjugating each one to increase the shikigami available to them,
until they are finally able to command all ten shikigami.
You done?
You're really strong, just like that woman from earlier.
Even though you're young.
You're all beat up, yet you give me no openings to get close.
Though, with all that bleeding, I won't even have to do anything.
Thing is, this subjugation can be done with multiple people.
Though conducting the subjugation with multiple people voids it afterward.
Which means the ritual becomes pointless to the sorcerer themselves.
Still, even if it is pointless, there are ways to use it.
Who's that?
They're being real flashy.
To continue,
while the shikigami can't be used without first subjugating it,
the user can summon them as many times as necessary
for the purpose of subjugating them.
You don't mean...
In all of sorcerer history, there's never been
anyone who managed to subjugate this one.
Do you know why the Gojo clan and the Zenin clan are on bad terms?
Are they actually on bad terms in the first place?
Sparks are constantly flying.
Since the Edo era? Or the Keicho era?
I forget when,
but the heads of the clans at the time got serious during a spectated match,
and they both died.
Were the heads of those clans...
One was someone like me who possessed both the Six-Eyes and the Limitless technique.
And the other used the same technique as you, Megumi.
The Ten Shadows Technique.
Understand what I'm getting at?
That doesn't mean I can actually become a sorcerer capable of beating you.
I imagine the head of the clan used this in much the same way back then.
Sacred treasure swing and ring, ring.
Sukuna-sama?
Urgent business.
I see.
It won't be much longer before I'm free.
Do not slack on our preparations.
See you later, Uraume.
As you wish.
I'll be awaiting your return.
He tricked me!
He's starting that ritual!
And he's forcing me to participate in the damn thing with him!
Eight-Grip Sword...
Divergent Sila Divine General...
Makora.
See you later.
Yeah!
Sorry, Itadori.
Hey, you damn bastard!
I'll be dying first.
Give it your best.
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Oh, fuck you!
Damn it!
Wake up, you shitty sorcerer!
The technique of the curse user Shigemo Haruta
erases life's little daily miracles from his memory and stores them up.
That stock manifests as the markings under his eyes,
and when he is faced with a threat to his life, one miracle is released.
However, he is unaware of this fact himself.
Huh?
Suspended animation, huh?
I see.
So saving this piece of trash really was the right move.
He probably sucked this thing into the subjugation ritual along with him.
Once this trash dies, too, the ritual will be complete.
Then Fushiguro Megumi's death will be established, as well.
Don't die on me.
There are things I need you to do for me.
U-Um...
Silence.
For Fushiguro Megumi to survive,
I'll have to defeat this shikigami as an outsider,
and nullify his subjugation ritual.
Time for a tasting, then.
Dissect.
That sword...
It's the Sword of Exorcism, specialized in combating cursed spirits.
It's packed with the same positive energy generated by a reverse cursed technique.
If I was a cursed spirit,
that would have eliminated me on the first blow.
Tastes awful.
You wanna go?!
Oh?
You did something, didn't you?
What the hell?!
Now that felt odd.
Again?!
What is that?!
Run!
Help us!
We're falling!
Cursed energy?!
You've done it now!
You can see it!
You see my technique!
I knew it.
You're similar to Yamata no Orochi.
You follow my slices,
and attack with cursed energy...
Both started happening after that great wheel revolved.
The incantation of sacred treasures
and that great wheel both represent perfect cycles and harmony.
Which suggests that this shikigami's ability
is to adapt to anything and everything.
It's the ultimate late-throw rock-paper-scissors!
You might have defeated me in the state I was in back then.
Now you've fascinated me, Fushiguro Megumi!
Domain Expansion:
Malevolent Kitchen.
Sukuna's Domain, Malevolent Kitchen,
is unlike others in that
it does not cut out a separate space with a barrier.
Manifesting an innate domain without sealing it in a barrier
is like trying to paint a picture in the air without a canvas.
It's truly a divine feat.
To top it off, by adding a pact to allow its victims a path of escape,
it vastly increases the range of
its guaranteed-hit effect to a maximum 200-meter radius.
Though out of consideration for its effect on Fushiguro Megumi,
he has currently restrained the effect to a 140-meter radius limited to the surface.
Anything?
Nope. No signal.
Same.
I don't think we need to worry that much, though.
Huh?
Remember the guy with the megaphone? He should be—
Sukuna's slices are comprised of two types.
"Fillet" attacks things with cursed energy in the range of his guaranteed-hit effect.
"Dissect" attacks things without cursed energy.
Both rain down endlessly upon everything until Malevolent Kitchen disappears.
The only sure way to defeat Makora is to bury it
with the first use of an attack before it can adapt.
Fillet would have fulfilled those conditions,
but that wouldn't necessarily hold true
if it had adapted to slices in general,
rather than to Dissect.
Makora was close to finishing its regeneration.
Fuga (Open).
What are you looking at?
Begone.
E-Excuse me, then!
I really am lucky!
For another day...
I survived!
Shigemo's stock of miracles
had been exhausted in his battle with Kento Nanami.
Oh, it's nearly time.
Fushiguro!
I just saw Itadori for a moment...
No, was it Sukuna?!
Hey, brat, be sure to savor this.
Die!
Only me!
Right now!
I have to go.
I have to fight.
Otherwise, I'll just be...
a murderer.
This has gotten really bad!
I'll count prime numbers to calm down.
One, two, three... uh, nine...
You missed five and seven.
Next time, Judgement.
You'll turn into a panda if you don't watch!
You really are an animal...