Don't go, Kugisaki!
Remember what Nanami said?
The whole reason they kept quiet about Ieiri—
...was to prevent me from doing something reckless like this, right?
That's probably why these people were late getting here, too.
But even so...
I can't be the only one going back when those two are out there fighting.
W-Wait!
Kugisaki!
I guess I should have asked Dagon to leave a few more humans for me.
Still, this is plenty!
Damn it!
Are you okay?!
Y-Yeah!
Shit!
Nice!
She's wary of both my hands.
She must have heard the report from that 7:3 sorcerer, then.
You're no fun.
But I'm only a double.
I can still alter my own shape,
but I can't tweak transfigured humans
or interfere with the souls of others.
So thanks for wearing your nerves down all on your own!
I already told you,
that won't work on me.
You know that, right?
Sometimes you still have to try, despite knowing it's futile!
For you.
Hairpin!
She's jumping down?
What does this girl hope to achieve?
Here's another!
Hairpin!
She used the nails that had fallen before!
I've been thinking about it
ever since I heard about your technique.
I bet this one will work nicely on you.
Resonance!
Kugisaki?!
No way...
No way!
Itadori Yuji wasn't my only natural enemy?!
That's odd.
I just felt my cursed energy explode far away from here.
The pressure from your cursed energy is also lackluster,
and you could have just taken hold of me earlier, too.
You're...
some kind of double who can't use its technique, aren't you?
Correct.
Her technique's aftereffects are lingering a long time!
I still can't get my body to move like it should!
Kugisaki...
Thank you.
I couldn't save anyone.
I caused everyone's efforts to end in vain.
But even so...
You've let me believe that I'm not alone!
Which is why...
I...
will kill you!
Here and now!
Now that Resonance is working,
it shouldn't fire off attacks as rapidly as before.
This is where the real battle begins!
No...
I'm running!
Huh?!
Hold it!
I could ignore it and head straight for floor B5,
but if I let that thing run free,
it'll just cause more issues later.
Underground?!
This is perfect!
I'll exorcise it and keep heading down to floor B5!
It split apart?!
Which one?
One of them should have the fatal portion of its soul for me to crush!
You fell for it!
Shit! I got tricked by its cursed energy!
There are two Mahitos?!
He had a double that was acting separately?!
So he's planning to merge it back in and heal himself!
Itadori?!
Run! Kugisaki!
Hit you dead-on!
You're in my way!
Kugisaki!
Now, then...
I wasn't able to completely finish off the 7:3 sorcerer with just one touch...
but what about her?
Die, damn it!
You're too naïve, Nobara.
You have to make sure you crush their chance to recover.
At the time...
You can do it!
I thought everyone in my village was crazy,
and I was convinced I was the only sane one.
You'll be using it until sixth grade, you know.
Are you sure?
Yeah!
I know that's what my mother said,
but I chose the blue backpack anyway.
We moved to this village at the same time I was starting elementary school.
My parents were worried about the inconveniences of the countryside,
but I didn't like being separated from my friends.
There were nineteen students in the whole school.
Not just one class.
Everyone had either a red or a black backpack.
I liked both red and black,
but apparently everyone hated blue.
Huh?
Th-Thank you.
Hey,
let's trade backpacks, Fumi!
Huh?
Let's trade!
I'm number one in Japan!
Hey! Kugisaki!
Uh-oh!
Kugisaki! You again?!
Shut up, old geezer!
Don't come near me!
My backpack came back to me before the day was over.
I hate all backpacks in the first place.
Huh?
After that day, Nobara started coming over to my house a lot
and playing video games with my father.
You've gotten better at aerials.
Nobara hated the other villagers.
It's such a small village
that it's harder to be strangers than friends.
I thought, "Isn't that a good thing?"
When the old lady next door brought red rice
to celebrate my first period several years later,
I finally understood the creepiness that Nobara was referring to.
Fumi!
I found a secret base!
Sometimes Nobara would say things you wouldn't expect from a child,
but then she'd suddenly say things like that, too.
We're living here starting today!
Thinking back, those were probably things she picked up from someone else.
Like her mother, maybe.
Here it is!
Nobara's so-called secret base was just someone else's house.
Yahoo!
Oh, you really did come by.
Welcome. It's cold out, isn't it?
The girl's name was Saori,
and she had moved into the village after I had.
We always visited her out of the blue,
and she always welcomed us without a hint of displeasure.
Now that I think about it, Saori was always at home.
Nobara changed after she met Saori.
Oh, yes! Why, yes!
You sound like Matsuko.
Fumi, let me practice braiding your hair!
Again?
Her speech grew softer,
and it felt like she started to become more refined.
We were both outsiders,
but everything was different between me and Saori.
A little while after that,
things at Saori's house started to look strange.
There was piled up trash, graffiti,
snow that was clearly piled up in front of it by someone else, and so on.
It made her nice house start to feel unsettling.
Not too much longer after that,
Saori moved away.
I saw her off together with Nobara,
but I can't remember what the weather was like or what anyone said at the time.
I only remember Nobara bawling with tears streaming down her face.
I realized she could cry, too,
and the shock of that meant nothing else made it into my mind.
In June of this year,
Nobara was set to start going to high school in Tokyo.
She fought with her grandma over it, and that apparently caused some delays.
Okay! I'm never coming back here again!
So make sure you get out of this village at some point, too, Fumi!
Sure.
The awful thought of, "So she won't cry for me," crossed my mind,
and left me unable to speak.
We never spoke of Saori again after that day.
Fumi.
Let's make sure all three of us are together when we meet again.
Yeah!
Saori, why don't you rest for a bit?
I can't. The proofs are due today...
Or I guess yesterday at this point?
It's still today until morning.
Ugh, I have a pimple!
Shibuya's in trouble. Terrorism, I guess?
Senpai, were you ever hoping to get married?
Huh? Where'd this come from?
Well, I was just thinking it wasn't supposed to turn out like this.
I moved out into the sticks during my second year of middle school.
A parent's work transfer?
No, my mother was a crazy woman who was into organics and spiritualism.
I think I get the picture.
While I was there, I met these two girls...
Seven years younger, I guess, and this one, Nobara, really took a liking to me.
I was an only child,
so I thought Nobara was just the cutest thing ever,
and I forced myself to act like an older sister, hoping she'd like me.
I even served them tea.
For first graders!
That's kind of cute.
I never did give them my contact info, though.
I was afraid of us slowly growing further apart,
and she really cried her eyes out when I left the village.
But...
I wonder if she would be disappointed to see how I am now.
I hope Nobara's doing well.
I wonder where she is and what she's up to now.
"Everyone in the village was crazy."
That notion was never true.
But the crazy ones have the louder voices,
and make it seem like they're all there is
so they can trample all over other people's lives.
Though I guess that wasn't entirely the case.
I'm sorry, Fumi.
I couldn't keep our promise.
Itadori.
Tell everyone for me:
Life wasn't so bad!
Kugisaki?
When I first stepped off at Tokyo Station,
I was a bit grossed out because the air smelled like I was standing behind a truck.
Now it doesn't bother me at all, though.
Next time, Right and Wrong, Part 3.
I guess life's all about the dirt we pick up.