Jeez, what a mess.
There's another Veil centered here underground
that also traps non-sorcerers inside.
Oops! Excuse me!
Hup, hup.
I kinda get what they're after.
Guess I'll play along.
They're making Mr. Gojo do this alone?!
I mean, I get the reasoning,
but there has to be something we can do!
Maybe go in as backup?
Yes.
That's why we're heading to Shibuya.
Oh, we are?
Give it back.
Excuse me?
Having you be his backup...
Gojo Satoru must be feeling pretty lavish right now.
You shouldn't treat him like some ordinary guy.
You're no ordinary lady either!
Oh dear, Ui Ui!
You're such a cuitie!
There you go again saying things you don't mean.
The family you claim to love so much
mei as well be a contract to you.
You know me so well.
I love that part of you.
Oh, my!
Can we go now?
Hello, Mei Mei here.
Oh?
Itadori, there has been a change of plans.
Another Veil like the one over Shibuya
has been cast over Meiji Jingumae Station.
That's where we are headed.
We'll be running. Try to keep up.
Right!
I see you guys came prepared.
There he is.
No excuses for losing this time, okay?
Likewise. I hope you have an
excuse ready for your first defeat.
The Veil covers the entire underground station
and traps civilians inside.
There is another Veil under it,
centered around the platform on B5,
which prevents sorcerers from entering.
The one who cast these Veils
must be located somewhere between the two.
Between? And not at the center?
We believe they're taking the risk of being outside the Veil
to enhance the strength of the barrier.
Two assistant supervisors have already been taken out.
Also, in between these barriers...
Well, we can't say for certain yet...
It's fine. Say it.
In between the barriers,
transfigured humans have been spotted.
What are we waiting for? We gotta hurry!
Hush!
Sister is currently sharing vision with the crows.
It takes incredible concentration, so be quiet.
It's fine, actually. You can talk.
She said it's fine.
Oh, come on!
I've got the gist of it.
Itadori.
Between killing a bunch of weak transfigured humans
and exorcising one strong cursed spirit,
which would you prefer?
Knowing you, I would bet it's the latter.
Here's a map of the underground station.
The transfigured humans are mulling about
and attacking people on level B4.
I think most of the civilians are at the platform on level B5.
You're not sure?
My crows are infused with cursed energy,
so they couldn't enter B5.
I'm guessing their plan is to force people to flee to B5.
Also, my crows were hunted down between B1 and B2.
That is where the one casting the Veil is.
It's unclear why they picked this specific location.
Do they plan to kill anyone who tries to escape,
or is it just the Veil's conditions?
We don't even know what they
hope to achieve by isolating level B5.
He's here, isn't he?
Down there somewhere.
I'm not sure.
My crows all got killed before I could confirm Patchface.
Though the presence of transfigured humans
would suggest that is likely.
I'm not so sure about splitting up,
but if we keep wasting time,
everyone on B4 will be wiped out.
The two of us will take Exit 7
directly to B4 and rescue the civilians.
If it gets too dangerous,
you head down there as well.
If I may be greedy,
I hope that by the time we reunite,
the Veil will be lifted, civilians will be freed,
and we will know what our opponent on B5 is after.
Don't worry, Miss Mei.
I won't lose to anything.
Munch, munch.
Munch, munch. Munch, munch.
What're you looking at?
Y-You're
Y-You're a j-juchu...
Y-You're a j-juchu... j-jujuchu...
Y-You're a j-juchu... j-jujuchu... juju...
Y-You're a j-juchu... j-jujuchu... juju... jujutsu sorcerer, right?
A jujutsu sorcerer, right?
I'm smart, I'll have you know.
The patchface curse is here, right?
Where is he?
Patch... face...
Patchface?
The one with stitches all over his face.
You think I'm stupid?! I know that much!
I told you, I'm smart!
Mahito's down below.
I'm here protecting the Veil.
Mahito...
I think Junpei also called him that.
No, the name doesn't matter right now.
Barrier techniques are quite complicated.
There are many who are strong
and still can't do them.
Though I'm both strong and capable.
This thing is responsible for the Veil? Both of them?
I doubt it.
Mahito's sorcery is bad.
Wait, he said he was "protecting" the Veil.
Which makes that object very suspicious.
I'll smash it just to be safe.
Did you know?
The humans he transfigures lose their flavor.
I can tell the difference!
Because I'm smart!
You curses are all the same.
You need to stop looking down on humans.
I take it y-you're not smart, huh?
You don't know what curse I am, do you?
Did you know?
The not-smart ones are the first to die in this world.
Uh, you're a grasshopper curse, right?
This guy... is smart!
Locust plague.
A large-scale disaster arising from an outbreak of locusts.
They consume not just crops,
but paper, clothes, huts, and anything plant-based.
A fully-grown locust eats
its own weight in food in a single day.
A swarm of locusts weighing a ton will consume
2,500 people's worth of food each day.
Grotesque mastication sounds echo unrelentingly.
Once the swarm has passed,
what remains is a wasteland
covered in black mucus excreted by the locusts,
creating a sight that is far from tranquil.
Mankind has long feared,
hated, and cursed such demonic pests.
It jumps around quick and bites down hard.
The fact that it can communicate
means it's not your average curse.
You just keep running away...
Which one are you?
I doubt he's using any tricks.
Which what?
Are you smart... or are you not smart?
I'm... smart!
Smart people don't really go around
calling themselves smart.
Really?!
This is a numbers battle.
Your two arms... versus my four.
My arms, jaw, and eyes
are all superior to those of humans.
So why?
Why am I the only one getting hit?
Still, I am the smarter one!
Locusts lay their eggs underground.
To facilitate this, they're capable of
extending their abdomen
which has a hard tip and can stretch up to
three times its normal length.
I win!
It did have a trick.
However, it didn't matter.
You've eaten people.
Ready to face the consequences?
The gap in their strength
was one that no trick could overcome.
Sister.
Yeah.
The Veil has been lifted.
Let's wait for Itadori and then head to B5.
Ko-guy was exorcised, huh?
We have a skilled sorcerer on our hands.
Sucks.
I wanted to fight, too.
Though I guess I can't.
Got a job to do.
That was impressive, Itadori.
What was?
To be honest, I thought you would have a harder time.
You're practically a first-grade already.
I haven't seen anyone get this far
without a technique since Kusakabe.
It wasn't Patchface.
If I was up against him, it wouldn't have gone as easily.
Sister is praising you! Accept it graciously!
Thank you very much! I'm honored!
Perhaps we're late.
Hey, you over there!
Are you okay?
Where are the other...
You don't need to do this. I'm not going anywhere.
I mean, if I ran away,
you guys would kill everyone here, right?
What are those two talking about?
You mean those four?
If you run away?
Do you know when Gojo Satoru is at his strongest?
Quit beating around the bush. Just say it.
You see,
it's when he's alone.
We'll kill them either way!
Stop it!
Hey!
Watch out!
It doesn't matter if you run.
Get back or you'll die.
So that's why they blocked the exits.
Now I can't tell if there are people
on the other side.
Any sorcerer alongside him just gets in his way.
So we'll surround him with non-sorcerers
who are even weaker.
Blood Manipulation:
Slicing Exorcism.
Take this!
Cursed technique reversal outputs
at least twice as much energy as amplification.
Using it without harming non-sorcerers
would be next to impossible.
He won't be able to use Blue at an output
that is effective against you either.
High-speed movement using Blue
would be difficult as well.
For non-sorcerers, it's instant death
if he bumps into them.
They would be dropping like flies.
In a situation like that,
Gojo Satoru will be forced on the defensive.
Domain Extension!
I see what you're doing.
Was it your resident curse user who gave you the idea?
Domain Extension.
It's somewhat similar to the
Simple Domain of New Shadow Style.
They extend their domains around themselves.
It may not have the sure-hit effect,
but it does neutralize any deployed techniques.
That would allow their attacks to hit me.
What do we do about his Infinite Void?
The only ones unaffected by Infinite Void
are Gojo Satoru himself and anyone he's in contact with.
Hypothetically speaking, even if
he is skilled enough to selectively trap you all,
most non-sorcerers would get crushed to death
between his domain and the Veil.
I'd say chances are ninety-nine percent
that he won't use his domain.
However, that means you mustn't
use your domains either.
If a lot of non-sorcerers end up trapped in your domain,
he might give up on them and use his own too.
And I assume you already know
who will win in a clash between domains.
Remember, you just need to get Gojo Satoru to focus.
On fighting curses and rescuing non-sorcerers.
Hey, stand up!
Come on, keep it together!
You're okay!
Here, take my hand.
I thought I told you not to run.
Must I do this to make you understand?
Man...
Honestly, I'm surprised.
What was that?
Making excuses already?
Not at all, baldy.
I'm surprised you thought you could beat me
with this sorry excuse of a plan.
I want you to hold out for at least twenty minutes.
You can leave the rest to me and the Prison Realm.
Let's play the list-the-good-things-
about-Gojo-Satoru game!
Yay!
He's strong!
He's just strong!
Next time, Shibuya Incident: Gate, Open.
He's rich, too, by the way.
Oh, you're such a kidder, Ma'am!
Seriously, don't discount what she said.