- Currently at Shibuya
- Hikarie
20:38
Shibuya, Hikarie, B3F
- Aoyama Cemetery
20:39
Aoyama Cemetery
- SFX
- Some Ordinary Guy
Some Ordinary Guy
- Team Mei Mei
Team Mei Mei
Mei Mei, First-Grade Sorcerer
Ui Ui
Itadori Yuji (Promotion Evaluation On Hold)
- Shibuya Platform
20:40
Tokyo Metro, Shibuya Station
B5F, Shin-toshin Line Platform
- Episode Title
Episode 32
The Shibuya Incident
- Map
Platform
- Meiji-jingumae Exit 2
20:51
Tokyo Metro, Meiji-jingumae Station
Exit 2
Platform
- Metro
21:03     Tokyo Metro, Meiji-jingumae Station, B2F
- Well, duh
You look just like one
- Shin-toshin Line
21:14
Tokyo Metro, Meiji-jingumae Station
B5F, Shin-toshin Line Platform
- Meiji-jingumae B4F
20:15
Tokyo Metro, Meiji-jingumae Station, B4F
- Well, duh (2)
Isn't that why I'm here?
- Bang
Bang
Can't Break It
Eek!
Bang
Can't Break It
Eek!
Bang
Can't Break It
Eek!
- heH
Heh
- Infinite Void
Veil
Infinite Void
Ack!
Veil
Infinite Void
Ack!
Veil
Infinite Void
Ack!
Veil
Infinite Void
Next Episode
Shibuya Incident: Gate, Open