Heads up!
Yep, it's working.
Ugh, what the heck was that?
Automatic selection of targets for your technique?
Yup.
Though, to be precise, I'm the target for the technique.
I've automated what I used to do manually.
In addition to cursed energy,
it can discern an object's danger level based on
its mass, velocity, and shape.
It'd be nice if it could detect poisons too,
but that'll take some time.
Now I should be able to keep my Limitless active
almost perpetually with minimal resources.
Having it perpetually active will fry your brain.
I'll also have reverse cursed technique
running around the clock,
constantly giving it a fresh brain to work with.
I've finally minimized all the necessary hand signs.
Multiple simultaneous activations of Red and Blue
is coming along nicely as well.
The only things left are Domain Expansion
and long-distance teleportation.
If we set up a clear course around the school,
I might be able to get that down too.
Shoko, could you lend me some lab rats?
Uh...
Satoru became "the strongest."
Suguru, have you lost weight?
You okay?
He handled all his missions alone.
Shoko was never sent out on
dangerous missions in the first place,
which naturally meant I was sent on missions alone more often too.
It's just heat fatigue.
I'll be fine.
Had too much somen?
Things were busy that summer.
Perhaps due to all those frequent disasters last year.
Curses were springing up like maggots.
Exorcise.
Consume.
Over and over.
Exorcise. Consume.
It's a taste nobody knows.
The taste of a curse.
Like swallowing a rag used to wipe up shit and vomit.
Who am I doing this for?
Exorcise.
Consume.
I've been telling myself ever since that day.
What I witnessed was nothing out of the ordinary.
Just the ugliness of the masses.
Despite knowing that, I still chose to be
a sorcerer who saves others.
Don't lose your way.
Follow through with your duty as the strong.
Damn monkeys.
Geto!
Haibara.
I hope you're doing well!
You want a drink?
What? No, I couldn't possibly...
Cola, please!
I'm going pretty far away for tomorrow's mission.
Is that so?
I'll be expecting souvenirs, then.
Of course!
Would you like something sweet or salty?
Satoru might eat some too,
so get something sweet, I guess?
Got it!
Haibara, do you think being a sorcerer
was the right path?
Isn't it too hard?
Honestly...
I'm not one to think too hard
about my path in life.
I'm satisfied as long as I can follow it
to the best of my ability!
Yeah.
You're right.
Are you Geto?
What type of women do you like?
May I know who you are?
I like girls who eat a lot!
Oh?
Haibara...
It's okay. She's not a bad person.
I'm a great judge of character!
You say that sitting next to me?
Yes!
He was being sarcastic, you know.
I'll be off, then.
Is he your junior?
It's cute how frank he is.
He should be more suspicious of people as a sorcerer.
So, are you not going to answer?
I need you to answer my question first.
Who are you?
Special-grade sorcerer, Tsukumo Yuki.
Ring any bells?
Oh.
You're the...
Oh, wow! What have you heard about me?
You're the special-grade
who never takes on any missions.
Just a waste who does nothing but
wander around overseas.
Man, I hate Jujutsu Tech.
She's sulking.
Kidding.
Though it is true that Jujutsu Tech and I don't see eye to eye.
What they do here is treat the symptoms.
I want to treat the cause.
How does that work?
Instead of hunting down curses,
I want to create a world where curses are never born.
Care for a little lesson?
What are curses to begin with?
They're creatures that are formed from the
build-up of cursed energy leaking from humans.
Excellent.
Therefore, we have two ways to
create a world where curses aren't born.
First is to eliminate cursed energy from all of humanity.
Second is to make it possible for every human
to control their cursed energy.
I thought the first one had a pretty good chance of working.
It even had a proof of concept.
Really?
It's someone you're familiar with.
Zenin Toji.
I've seen several cases where Heavenly Restriction
has reduced a person's cursed energy,
but only to the level of a normal human.
He was the only one to eliminate it entirely.
That wasn't the only intriguing thing about him, either.
He could perceive curses with his five senses
even without any cursed energy.
By eliminating cursed energy,
his body became sharpened to the point
that he developed a resistance to curses.
He truly was superhuman.
Don't feel bad about losing to him.
I wanted to try studying him, but he blew me off.
It's a real shame we lost him.
Cases of Heavenly Restriction are few and far between,
so I'm currently favoring the second route.
To make it possible for every human
to control their cursed energy.
Did you know? Curses are never born from sorcerers.
Obviously, that doesn't include cases
where the sorcerer turns into a curse after death.
Sorcerers leak very little cursed energy
compared to non-sorcerers.
It's partly due to the difference in
consumption and capacity of cursed energy,
but the main reason is its flow.
Sorcerers are always channeling
cursed energy throughout their bodies.
In layman's terms, if all of humanity were sorcerers,
curses would never be born.
In that case, why not just kill every non-sorcerer.
Geto.
That is an option.
But...
In fact, that might be the easiest way.
Keep culling non-sorcerers and force them to adapt
into sorcerers as a strategy for survival.
Basically forcing them to evolve using fear and danger,
the same way birds gained wings.
Unfortunately, I'm not crazy enough to do that.
Do you hate non-sorcerers, Geto?
I don't know.
I always thought sorcerers existed to protect non-sorcerers.
But lately, the value of non-sorcerers
has been wavering in my mind.
The preciousness of the weak. The ugliness of the weak.
I can no longer tell the difference between them.
Part of me despises non-sorcerers,
and part of me wants to reject that feeling..
If being a sorcerer is like running a marathon, then I can't see what lies at the finish line.
I don't know how I truly feel.
The answer is neither.
You're not at that stage yet.
The part of you that despises non-sorcerers,
and the part of you that rejects it.
They're both just possibilities that you're considering.
Whatever your true feeling is,
it's something you have yet to decide.
Later, then.
I was hoping I could talk to Gojo, too.
Looks like I missed him today.
I hope the three of us can all get along
as fellow special-grades.
I'll pass that along to Satoru.
Oh, right, one last thing.
You don't need to worry about
the Star Plasma Vessel.
Maybe there was another Star Plasma Vessel all along,
or maybe a new one has been born.
Either way, Tengen is stabilized.
Of course.
Oh, I didn't get his type.
The mission was to exterminate a weak
second-grade curse. It was supposed to be easy!
Fuck!
The Birthplace Deity...
Faith of the locals made it stronger.
This was a first-grade case!
You need to rest for now, Nanami.
Satoru has taken over the mission.
Why don't we just leave
everything up to him at this point?
If being a sorcerer is like running a marathon...
What if all that lies at the finish line
is a mountain of corpses of fellow sorcerers...
What is going on here?
What do you mean?
These two are responsible for the latest incidents!
No, they're not.
These two are crazy!
They attacked the villagers with their weird powers again!
I've already exterminated the cause of those incidents.
My grandson was nearly killed by these two!
That's because he—
Shut up, you monsters!
You're just like your parents!
I knew we should've killed you at birth!
It... It's okay.
The part of you that despises non-sorcerers,
and the part of you that rejects it.
Whatever your true feeling is...
Let's step outside for a moment, shall we?
...it's something you have yet to decide.
What is happening?!
Why?!
No!
What?
Don't make me repeat myself.
Suguru killed everyone in the village and—
I heard you the first time!
That's why I asked.
Suguru's old house was empty as well.
Judging from the bloodstains and residuals,
he might have killed his parents—
Like hell he did!
Satoru.
I don't understand what's going on, either.
Need a light?
'Sup.
If it isn't the criminal.
What brings you here?
Just testing my luck, I guess.
Any chance the charges are false?
Asking just in case.
Nope. Unfortunately not.
I'll ask another, then.
Why'd you do it?
I'm going to create a world of only sorcerers.
Yeah, I don't get it.
I'm not a child.
I'm not holding out hope that everyone will understand.
Sulking over the idea
that no one will understand you
sounds pretty childish to me, though.
Hey, Gojo?
Geto's here.
Yeah, Shinjuku.
No way. I don't wanna get killed.
Explain yourself, Suguru.
You already heard from Shoko, didn't you?
That's all there is to it.
So you're just going to kill everyone
who's not a sorcerer?
Even your parents?!
I can't allow my parents to be an exception.
Besides, my family isn't limited to just them anymore.
That's not what I'm asking!
I thought we weren't allowed to kill if there's no point to it!
There is a point to it. Significance, too.
You could even call it a cause.
Yeah, right!
Killing all non-sorcerers
to create a world of only sorcerers?!
You know that's impossible!
There's no point in chipping away at something
you can't possibly do!
How arrogant.
What?
You could do it, Satoru.
Yet you would try to convince someone else
that it's impossible to do something that's possible for you?
Are you the strongest because you're Gojo Satoru?
Or are you Gojo Satoru because you're the strongest?
What exactly are you getting at?
If I could be you, wouldn't my foolish ideals
become reasonable possibilities?
This is the path I've chosen.
All that's left is to follow it to the best of my ability.
If you want to kill me, then kill me.
There would be a point to that.
Why didn't you pursue him?
You're actually asking me that?
No, it's fine.
My bad.
Teach, I'm strong, right?
Yeah, brazenly so.
Me being strong isn't enough, apparently.
I can only save those who allow themselves to be saved.
I thought the Star Religious Group was dissolved.
It's a different group with similar roots.
It still looks like a religious group on the surface.
Don't like it?
No, it doesn't matter as long as I can
collect curses and money.
Are you really going out dressed like that?
Why not? A little showmanship goes a long way.
Master Geto!
Watch closely.
They're all there, right?
All the branch directors,
representatives, and the president.
All the big donors too.
Check, check.
Ladies and gentlemen, sorry to keep you waiting.
Now, I'll keep this brief.
As of this moment, this organization belongs to me.
We'll have a new name as well.
So everyone, please be sure to obey me.
Now, that's not good.
Oh, I know!
Mr. Sonoda, could you please come to the stage?
Yes! You there!
Now, let's try this again.
I hate monkeys.
You will obey me,
That is the true feeling I chose.
filthy monkeys.
You're Fushiguro Megumi, right?
Who are you?
And what's with that look on your face?
You look just like him, is all.
My own issue.
So, about your dad...
He's from a big-shot sorcerer family
called the Zenin clan,
but the reason he ran away and had you
makes him a scumbag even by my standards!
You have the ability to see the unseen,
and the power to manipulate it as well, right?
You've noticed the talent within yourself too, yeah?
The Zenin clan loves talent like that.
Most become aware of it at around
four to six years of age.
A ripe time to sell, indeed!
You, my dear Megumi, are your dad's
ace against the Zenin clan!
Pisses you off, doesn't it?
So I took care of that dad of yours by ki—
I don't care.
I have no interest in where he is
or what he's doing.
Haven't seen him in years.
Barely remember his face.
Though I get the general idea
from what you just said.
Tsumiki's mother hasn't come home
for a while now, either.
Ah, Megumi's back!
That means they're done with us
and are off enjoying themselves elsewhere.
Are you really a first grader?
Well, whatever.
If you ever wanna know about your dad,
feel free to ask me.
Hup.
I think you'll find it interesting.
Now, on to the main point.
What do you wanna do?
Go to the Zenin clan?
What will happen to Tsumiki?
Will she be happy there? It all depends on that.
No.
A hundred percent no.
That I can assure you.
Okay!
You can leave it to me, then.
I might need you to push yourself a bit, though.
Do your best!
Get stronger.
Strong enough to keep up with me.
Mr. Gojo!
So even Teach sleeps sometimes, huh?
Of course he does. What kinda nonsense is that?
Mr. Gojo!
Oh, he's awake!
Hey, isn't this one of those expensive chairs?
Please don't fall asleep after calling all of us here.
Hey, no fair! I get it next, okay?!
Hey! Hurry up!
What are you smiling about?
Don't be mean! Move it!
It's nothing.
How do you write "motto" in kanji?
Wait, you use katakana? It's a foreign word?
Next time, It's Like That.
I guess you learn something new every day!