One Year Later
August 2007
Episode 29
Premature Death
She's sulking...
O
h
i didn't
get his type
Investigation Report on Murders Involving a Student
vv
Subject of Investigation: Geto Suguru, Third-Year Student at Jujutsu Tech
Incident Overview
Date: September 23, 2007, around 9:00 PM.
Location: ■■■ Township (former ■■■ village), in ■■■ prefecture
Discovery: The person assigned (Geto) did not return after 5 days
of mission commencement. An assisting supervisor was dispatched,
who found devastation on-site.
Extent of Damage: 112 fatalities found in the former ■■■ village.
Overview of the Mission
Investigation in the former ■■■ village.
The settlement had a long history of mysterious missing persons cases.
Information from the client and our own investigations revealed that
unexplained deaths occurred frequently.
As approximately 80% were believed to be caused by cursed spirits,
Geto was tasked with finding and exorcising them.
Subject of Investigation: Geto Suguru, Third-Year Student at Jujutsu Tech
1.  Incident Overview
Date: September 23, 2007, around 9:00 PM.
Location: ■■■ Township (former ■■■ village), in ■■■ prefecture
Discovery: The person assigned (Geto) did not return after 5 days
of mission commencement. An assisting supervisor was dispatched,
who found devastation on-site.
Extent of Damage: 112 fatalities found in the former ■■■ village.
2.  Overview of the Mission
Investigation in the former ■■■ village.
The settlement had a long history of mysterious missing persons cases.
Information from the client and our own investigations revealed that
unexplained deaths occurred frequently.
As approximately 80% were believed to be caused by cursed spirits,
Geto was tasked with finding and exorcising them.
On September 19 (time unknown), a massacre occurred.
112 residents died, and a fire destroyed 70% of the village. (By the time
Jujutsu Tech staff arrived on September 23, there were no survivors and
thus no eyewitnesses.)
Investigations confirm that all of them were killed by a cursed spirit
whose residuals match Geto Suguru's Curse Manipulation.
It is assumed that after the massacre, Geto set the village on fire and
fled the scene.
His motives are currently unknown.
According to the village's personnel records, he was not related to any
of the victims. Additionally, it was discovered that a family of sorcerers
used to live in the village, which could have been a part of his motive.
Follow-up Actions
Geto is currently on the run.
In accordance with Article 9 of Jujutsu Regulations, he is now
considered a curse user and subject to execution.
On September 19 (time unknown), a massacre occurred.
112 residents died, and a fire destroyed 70% of the village. (By the time
Jujutsu Tech staff arrived on September 23, there were no survivors and
thus no eyewitnesses.)
Investigations confirm that all of them were killed by a cursed spirit
whose residuals match Geto Suguru's Curse Manipulation.
It is assumed that after the massacre, Geto set the village on fire and
fled the scene.
His motives are currently unknown.
According to the village's personnel records, he was not related to any
of the victims. Additionally, it was discovered that a family of sorcerers
used to live in the village, which could have been a part of his motive.
4.  Follow-up Actions
Geto is currently on the run.
In accordance with Article 9 of Jujutsu Regulations, he is now
considered a curse user and subject to execution.
Investigations confirm that all of them were killed by a cursed spirit
whose residuals match Geto Suguru's Curse Manipulation.
residuals match Geto Suguru's Curse Manipulation.
subject to execution.
A high schooler?
KF
Many Objected
October 19, 2018
Next Episode
It's Like That