Getting irritated at my own failings
never has been and never will be
a part of my life.
I will simply
confront the evils that force this reality upon us,
and I will simply...
How dare they.
You know my technique, right?
I can manipulate crows. That's it.
Weak, isn't it?
That's why I trained hard when I was young,
so I could fight even without a technique.
Being able to dominate you like this
tells me that my efforts were not in vain.
Wait! I'll pull out right now!
So please, spare me!
Quiet.
Sister is not done talking.
I always told myself that techniques
don't decide a sorcerer's worth.
But you know what?
I had hit my limit.
Physical abilities and cursed energy
enhancements only go so far.
I was crushed!
And because of that, I decided to give
my technique another shot,
and bloomed into the
first-grade sorcerer that I am today.
Applaud.
Now I'll kill you.
I just wanted to kill some time chatting.
Please forgive me!
I'll never do it again!
So please! Please spare my life!
Ui Ui,
can you tell me what is the value of a life
and how would you measure it?
Of course!
The answer is how useful that life is to you!
Thank you.
And you?
I think... u-uh...
You can't even describe the scale you use
to measure the lives you hunt down.
That's why you lost.
Coincidentally, I measure lives
by their potential assets.
Wait.
The anti-sorcerer Veil is
the only one that got lifted, right?
But didn't we break three of these,
including the one Ino broke?
Either they used all three to lower one Veil,
or the other two were dummies.
Either way, sorcerers are now free
to move into Shibuya.
That just leaves the Veil trapping Mr. Gojo,
and the Veil trapping civilians.
I wanted to interrogate this geezer,
but he'll be out for a while.
We should rejoin Ino and—
Ino!
The Veil's lifted.
What now, Granny?
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What do we do now?
With Gojo Satoru out of the play,
it matters little.
Go down and kill the sorcerers.
Grandson?
Who the hell do you think
you're ordering around, old hag?
What is going on?!
I only summoned the body's information!
Summoned?
Oh, so that's why.
I've always made it a point
not to summon the soul's information
precisely to prevent accidents like this.
I'm not exactly sure what's going on,
but my body's special.
I'd say this guy's soul lost to my body.
The soul lost to the body?! Impossible!
That is absurd!
I gotta kill sorcerers, huh?
Let's start with you.
Mr. Ijichi got attacked?
That's what it sounded like on the phone with Nitta.
It must have happened
after he left Fushiguro's group.
We shouldn't leave him alone right now.
Nobara, you take Akari to Mr. Ijichi's location.
Without any signal, the assistant supervisors
are critical for communication.
I doubt that dumbass would ever lose,
but this whole situation is smelling even fishier.
I'll handle things over here.
Damn geezer's totally useless.
Get me some booze!
Ignore him.
Now go.
Right!
Once they're outside the Veil,
they'll be able to run if the worst happens.
How's Ino?
Can't say he's okay,
but he's not dead.
I'm gonna go beat them up.
Itadori!
I understand how you feel,
but calm down!
What's our priority right now?
Mr. Gojo.
The Veil has been lifted.
Those guys up there might have escaped already.
Let's get Ino out of here.
Take care of Ino for me.
I'll head to the station.
Right, that's actually the best move.
But operating alone in Shibuya right now...
All right. But...
If I die, you'll kill me, right?
Don't worry!
I've got Mechamaru with me!
Though I haven't heard from him in a while.
So long as you understand.
See you later.
Right!
Sister.
Looks like the Veil has been lifted.
Just the thought of how much
this favor is going to cost Gojo Satoru
gets my heart racing!
That was faster than expected.
Nitta, stop.
Oh, it's a girl in the suit this time!
I'm so happy!
I was getting sick of them all being guys.
Nitta, hide.
I'll wrap this up quick.
Pretend to hide in Bunkamura,
then keep going and slip through Tokyu.
Judging by what he said, he might be
the one who took out Mr. Ijichi.
Which means we need to hurry.
Gotcha!
Don't push yourself too hard, Kugisaki.
Whispering now, are we?
You've got me curious!
Aw, she went and hid.
Close!
Throwing the fight like
you threw away your weapon?
Oh, we've met before, haven't we?
Cursed tool users prefer fighting from a distance.
I gotta get in close!
Who are you again?
Shooting nails is dangerous, you know!
I can make it even more dangerous.
Ow!
Hey, so she wasn't hiding!
Nitta!
Shoot!
Why, you!
The sword he dropped outside?!
How did it get here?!
Whoops! You missed!
Hairpin!
Nitta!
Man, you really are dangerous.
Oh, did it hit your chin?
Can't stand?
Hey, can you stand?
C'mon, I'm talking to you!
You know, you've gotten an
awful lot stronger since we last met.
I almost didn't recognize you.
But y'know what?
Being strong isn't enough to win in this world!
Especially against my technique.
Though, I don't really
understand it all that well either.
Now, which of you should I kill first?
Wh-What...
Gotta keep talking!
...are you after?
Buy as much time as possible!
Oh, I think they said something
about sealing Gojo Satoru.
I'm asking you!
Oh, me?
If someone who loves soccer and excels at it
was born in a world without soccer,
what would they want?
Never mind. I can't explain it.
I mean, do I even need a reason?
Who cares as long as it's fun, right?
Nothing else matters as long as I'm having fun!
Wouldn't you agree?
Stop it!
Make me stop!
Stop me from committing any more cli—
Ah, I flubbed it.
And my throat's blocked...
Whoa!
You can't even stand.
Yeah, yeah.
I wonder if it's okay...
to kill people in suits that aren't black?
He came to Shibuya with Fushiguro...
Mr. Nanami?
Come on now, read the room!
Why are you strutting this way?
Can't you see I've got this girl hostage?!
No!
She ran away.
How many allies do you have and where?
I dunno!
Huh? Did I hit a wall?
It didn't cut him?!
How many allies and where?
I dun—
I'd be dead!
If it weren't for my technique, I'd be dead!
I-I need to run!
How many and where?!
I told you, I don't—
Not on my watch!
Outta my way, dammit!
On my way here, I found several of our
assistant supervisors dead.
That was you, wasn't it?
I-I'm sorry.
He's in a different league.
That's a first-grade sorcerer for you.
Let's make our way to Miss Nitta.
Oh my, who do we have here?
It's been a while, Miss Mei.
Quite the thing to say after sending
assassins after me, Geto.
How is he still alive?
Did Gojo mess up last year?
Were Gojo and Geto in on
this whole commotion together?
No, definitely not.
Gojo could kill every human in this country all by himself.
He doesn't need anyone's help or any petty tricks.
For the record, I had my money on you over Gojo.
Your nihilistic smile was quite charming.
That I have to kill you is a bitter shame.
It really is.
This Geto is most likely a fake.
The feeling is mutual, Miss Mei.
To think I must kill someone I looked up to.
Curse Manipulation?!
Did I read this wrong?
Special-Grade Disease Curse: Smallpox Deity.
I used up my stock of curses last year,
but I assure you, the quality hasn't suffered.
I think I'll keep the humans on B5
just for good measure.
I'll be waiting down this line.
If you manage to exorcise that,
I'll take you on.
Domain Expansion?!
This could be troublesome.
Grave.
I'm trapped?
Is this a coffin?
Sister!
Three.
Two.
I wonder how many years it has been
since something actually threatened my life.
Sister!
There's nobody here!
Weren't there supposed to be a ton of
people trapped down here?
So Mr. Ijichi's okay, then?
I did what I could. Don't forget,
he once trained to be a sorcerer as well.
Anyway, it seems you all
really haven't heard about Gojo yet.
Probably because we went indoors right away.
Holding out even after being sealed
sounds like him all right.
You two, please wait here for the rescue.
I'll join the Zenins and head down to B5.
I'll go, too!
No, you won't.
I'm the minimum level required for the fights ahead.
You would only get in the way.
Please wait here.
Itadori Yuji!
I'll avenge my brothers!
Mr. Ijichi, we'll help you with work!
It's fine. I'm fine.
Don't be shy!
We're from the digital native generation!
Excel, PowerPoint, we know it all!
I mean it. I really am fine.
Next time, Red Scale.
What's "merge cells"?
Just click it.
Please, just go away!