It's from Kuroi.
Wh-What do we do?!
Kuroi has...
Kuroi has been...
There's always a chance the worst could happen.
You're much faster than me,
so go on ahead! Hurry to Riko's side!
I'm sorry. This was my mistake.
Really?
I don't think this even counts as a mistake.
I underestimated how much our enemies would value Kuroi.
Their next move will probably be offering to arrange an exchange for her.
Something like trading Amanai for Kuroi,
or saying they'll kill Kuroi if we don't kill Amanai.
But we have the leverage in any negotiations since we have Amanai.
As long as they set up the location for the deal, we can make it work out.
I'm taking Amanai back to Jujutsu Tech now.
We can have Shoko or someone stand in as her body double.
H-Hold on!
I'm going to this deal, too!
I still can't trust you two yet!
Huh?! You're still saying that after all this, you—
Even if you do manage to save her...
What if Kuroi isn't back before I assimilate with Master Tengen?
I haven't...
I haven't even said goodbye to her!
The kidnapper will reach out to us eventually.
If they seem like they're smarter than we expect,
and bringing you with us is likely to hurt Kuroi's chance of survival...
then we will leave you behind.
All right. That works.
In exchange,
if you get scared partway through and want to go home, we'll just ignore you.
Bear that in mind.
Mensore!
I can't believe I got captured by the Star Religious Group,
and by a non-sorcerer at that.
I'm ashamed of myself.
You couldn't help it if they caught you off-guard.
Part of the blame lies with me, too.
Was I really caught off-guard?
I thought I was on high alert after the incident with Q.
Kuroi!
I still don't have much recollection of being attacked.
And you all came here by plane?
Were you okay?
You weren't attacked?
Satoru has good eyes.
Before we took off, he checked over all the passengers and staff,
as well as the inside and outside of the plane.
And while we were in the air, I had my cursed spirit keep watch outside.
It was safer than using a land route.
I'm more curious as to why they designated Okinawa for the exchange.
Probably to buy time, right?
Even if they fail to kill Riko-sama,
they could keep her from making tomorrow's full moon deadline.
If that were the goal,
they would choose a rural area with poor transit infrastructure.
You don't think they're planning to take over the airport, do you?
Maybe so.
But we'll be fine.
We're not the only ones who came here.
Clearly this isn't a mission fit for a first-year.
I'm psyched, though!
I want to show off in front of Geto, too!
Besides, I hear our upperclassmen are wearing themselves to the bone to protect an innocent young girl!
So we have to give it our all, too!
If a typhoon rolls in and shuts down the airports, our efforts will be for naught.
Sea cucumber, sea cucumber!
Gross! That's so gross!
Should we really be sightseeing like this?
Satoru's the one who suggested it.
He's probably showing consideration for Riko, in his own way.
Though it is getting close...
Satoru! It's time.
Oh, it's that time already?
Boo.
Suguru, let's head back tomorrow morning instead.
But...
The weather's holding steady, right?
Besides...
there are fewer curse users in Okinawa than there are in Tokyo.
Let's keep it a little more serious, Satoru.
It's better if the time limit on the bounty runs out while we're mid-flight, right?
Young lady, a starfish.
So it is!
Satoru.
You haven't released your technique since yesterday, have you?
You haven't slept, either.
And you don't plan to sleep tonight, do you?
Are you sure we don't need to go back to Jujutsu Tech?
It's not a problem.
Playing through 99 years of MomoTetsu was far more draining.
Besides, you're here, too.
Nanami, they said they're extending their stay another day!
You think something happened?!
Good work, everyone.
We're inside Jujutsu Tech's barrier now.
What a relief.
Yes.
Satoru.
You really worked hard this time.
I never wanna get stuck babysitting a brat again.
Huh?
Impossible!
We're inside Jujutsu Tech's barrier!
Have we met before?
Don't worry about it.
I'm terrible at remembering guys' names, too.
I once went to see the brat born into the Gojo clan with the Six Eyes on a lark.
Never before or after that had anyone noticed me standing behind them.
That is why I wore him down...
until his senses dulled.
Satoru!
I'm fine.
I didn't make it in time with my technique,
but it missed my vitals.
I then strengthened myself with cursed energy so the blade couldn't be drawn out at all.
It was like passing a safety pin through a knit sweater.
Seriously, I'm fine.
Prioritize Amanai.
I'll deal with this guy.
Suguru, you two get her to Master Tengen.
Satoru...
Be careful!
Let's go!
Right!
Who do you think you're talking to?
That's different from the blade he stabbed me with.
And where did that cursed spirit come from?
Too many unknowns, damn it!
The Star Plasma Vessel is gone.
I had hoped to take you down with that earlier attack. I guess I've gotten rusty.
The bounty on Amanai has already been taken down, you idiot.
Because I took it down, prideful bastard.
When facing people without openings like you,
you have to first create ups and downs leading to several false goals.
I laughed when those Star Religious Group men went to Okinawa.
It sucked that none of the sorcerers around her died,
but if I hadn't set that time limit on the bounty,
you wouldn't have released your technique until the very end.
That so?
He's fast!
And not just that.
I knew there was something off about him!
He has zero cursed energy!
He has a Heavenly Pact gifting him physical prowess!
I can't imagine anyone who knows my technique coming without a plan.
Is that cursed tool your precious trump card?
Sorry, but I won't let it get close!
Since he has no cursed energy, I can't read his presence.
And I can't just rely on instinct.
There's that cursed spirit wrapped around him.
I just need to follow its presence.
Even so, he's too damn fast!
Cursed Technique Amplification,
Maximum Output...
Blue!
Now there's no cover.
He can't launch surprise attacks.
Did he hide in the woods?
Are those...
Fly Heads?!
Was he keeping them inside that cursed spirit?
So you're using Fly Heads like chaff.
Now I can't tell where he is.
He's created a blind spot.
I should use Blue again...
No, wait! He's after...
Amanai!
His intuition is keen enough to sense me empty-handed.
There's no way your Six Eyes would overlook the unusual cursed energy oozing from this cursed tool.
Though that finally...
got you to focus on defense with your technique.
The Special-Grade Cursed Tool, Inverted Spear of Heaven.
Its effect is the forced release of any active techniques.
I think...
I'm getting my edge back now.
Lady Riko.
This is as far as I go.
Riko-sama, please...
Please...
Kuroi, I love you!
I always have, and I always will!
Me, too!
I love you, too!
So this is...
Yeah.
We're in Master Tengen's territory now.
This is the foundation of the nation's key barriers,
The Main Hall of the Tombs of the Star.
Once you descend the stairs,
pass through the gate and continue to the base of the big tree.
Then you'll be inside the special barrier that's separate from
the barrier surrounding Jujutsu Tech.
Only those invited are able to enter it.
Master Tengen will protect you until the assimilation.
That...
or we can turn back around and go home with Kuroi.
Huh?
When our teacher told us about this mission,
he called the assimilation "erasing."
He was trying to tell us to be aware of how heavy a sin that was.
Our teacher may be a muscle-brain,
but he often does roundabout things.
Satoru and I already talked it over before we met you.
What if the Star Plasma Vessel brat refuses to assimilate?
Then... the assimilation's off!
Are you sure about that?
Huh?
It might mean fighting Master Tengen, you know.
You scared?
It's fine. It'll all work out somehow.
We are the strongest.
No matter what decision you make,
we will guarantee your future.
I have...
always been special, since the day I was born.
Everyone kept telling me that I was different.
Being special was normal to me,
and I've lived my life trying to avoid danger
as much as possible for the sake of this day.
I don't really remember the day my mother and father died.
I no longer feel sad or lonely about that.
I figured everything would be fine,
even if I was taken away from everyone and assimilated.
That no matter how hard it was,
it would stop feeling sad and lonely one day.
But...
Honestly...
I want to be with everyone longer!
I want to go to all kinds of places with everyone!
I want to see all kinds of things and do more!
Let's go home, Riko.
Yeah!
Riko?
Okay, job's done.
You're free to go now.
Why are you here?
Why?
Oh, that's what you mean.
Because I killed Gojo Satoru.
Is that so?
Die!
They say it's never too late to start something,
but the bigger problem is always when to quit, not when to start.
"Please look forward to the next episode: Hidden Inventory 4!"
I can't even say that.