Kusakabe?
Hey! Kusakabe!
Found you!
Panda.
This is awfully different from what I heard.
Huh?
About Itadori.
Nah, that was Sukuna.
Itadori holds control over that body.
That's the current story, right?
Urk.
I'll tell you this now.
No matter what judgment gets doled out to Itadori later now that Gojo is gone,
I won't be taking your side.
I'm in favor of Itadori Yuji's execution.
Sorry about that.
You must be worn out, Ui Ui.
Shall we sleep in the same bed tonight?
What?! That's so improper!
Do you hate me when I'm improper?
No way!
Sorry, I got a call back.
Oh, Nee-sama...
Sorry for calling so late.
Oh, right, it's morning where you are.
Me?
In KL.
Yes, with Ui Ui's technique.
We nearly got ourselves killed, after all.
You should sell off any stocks in Japan and all your real estate in Tokyo.
I've already exchanged all of my yen.
Yes, do it right away.
I doubt any of the major developed nations will be spared from these negative events.
Japan is still the world's #3 economy, despite all else.
Well, I'll leave the arrangements up to you.
It's fine. You don't need to thank me.
Just keep me on the inside, like usual.
I look forward to working with you again.
Bread, bread, bread!
What's wrong, Nii?
Not feeling well?
I have to go.
Itadori Yuji...
What are you?
I have to know.
What am I?
Shall I save you,
Mahito?
Did he just say Geto?!
Give him back!
Give us back Gojo!
People believed catfish were connected to earthquakes
and told stories of such a monster up until the mid-Edo era.
They believed that when this "Onamazu" moved underground,
it caused earthquakes to occur.
What just happened?!
You thought you fell in, didn't you?
Though, from the outside, it looked like you fell back all on your own.
The greatest strength of Cursed Spirit Manipulation is its quantity of options.
I can utilize multiple cursed spirits semi-first-grade or higher,
and even if you analyze and overcome their techniques,
I can just send out new cursed spirits again.
Of course, I can also simply pile on attacks without giving you time for that.
This won't...
If his forces hadn't been divided
across Kyoto and Shinjuku during last year's Night Parade of a Hundred Demons,
he would have won instead of Okkotsu.
Though, I suppose that had nothing to do with you, did it?
Give him back!
I suppose I should say that even I am impressed.
Sukuna's vessel... is tough.
I knew that.
After all, I was born from you humans.
Shall we continue...
our discussion of the world to come?
Do you know about what they call a "Supreme Art"?
It's very much akin to the ultimate expression
of a cursed technique, aside from one's domain.
The Supreme Art of Cursed Spirit Manipulation is Uzumaki.
This combines the absorbed cursed spirits into one,
creating super-high-density cursed energy to attack your opponent with.
What are you laughing about?
Oh, sorry.
I just realized I had started acting like him.
We were talking about Uzumaki, yes?
Uzumaki is powerful,
but it also means throwing away the quantity
of options that serves as Cursed Spirit Manipulation's main strength.
So it wasn't very tempting to me at first.
After all, I thought it was just a way to recycle low-level cursed spirits.
But I was wrong.
It displays its true value
when a cursed spirit above semi-first-grade is used in Uzumaki—
and their technique is extracted.
How foolish.
Did you think I wouldn't notice the presence you felt?
Our signal!
The target is...
right below Nishimiya!
Tsk.
A sniper rifle, huh?
Nice.
I also agree that conventional weapons
should be proactively used when fighting a jujutsu sorcerer.
Back when I was captain of the youth basketball team,
I remember my mother would often dye my hair black.
In middle school, I met my mentor,
and I chose to become a jujutsu sorcerer
before ever holding a wooden or a bamboo sword in my hands,
let alone a real sword.
I swung my sword relentlessly.
Because I didn't want to be a burden on my mother.
Because I didn't want to die.
New Shadow Style...
Put it all in!
Everything I've experienced,
as well as my future to come!
Even if it means I'll never swing a sword again!
Quick Draw!
Supreme Art:
Uzumaki.
Wait!
New Shadow Style, huh?
I'm glad.
It's nice facing someone with a bit of knowledge.
Kusakabe!
There's no point if you're out in front, !
I couldn't help it!
Itadori...
It's you, right?
Panda!
Good, you're back to normal.
That man has Gojo Satoru...
and the Prison Realm, huh?
Apparently.
I don't know what he finds so fun about walking around with that public nuisance.
Who is he?
The shell is Geto Suguru.
I don't know what's inside.
Hey, Choso.
He's...
I have three parents.
My mother,
the cursed spirit that impregnated my mother,
and the man who mixed his blood into the affair...
The one who toyed with my mother...
The loathsome—
Looks like you've realized it.
So that's how it is!
Kamo Noritoshi!
Kamo?!
Noritoshi?!
Me?!
What?!
What's going on?!
The stain on the Kamo clan!
The worst sorcerer in all history!
If he's right, then whatever's inside Geto would be over 150 years old.
Outlandish barriers,
and possession of outlandish cursed tools...
As far as masterminds with a cursed technique to take over other bodies goes...
That seems appropriate, yeah.
Kamo Noritoshi is merely one of the many names I've had.
Call me whatever you like.
How dare you...
How dare you make me
try to kill Itadori?!
My little brother!
Stand down, third-rate.
Don't keep me waiting any longer.
Move it!
I'm his older brother!
It's a side effect of my technique.
I can feel any changes to my blood-related siblings,
no matter how far away they are.
My younger brothers died.
Death.
For every living being,
that is their last and greatest change.
In that moment,
I strongly sensed the death of Itadori Yuji, right before my eyes.
Which means that Yuji
must also be my blood-related younger brother!
If Kamo Noritoshi has been extending his life
by transferring bodies,
then it's not an impossible idea.
Which means I...
must use my full strength
to perform my duty as the older brother!
Blood Manipulation?!
So much pressure!
It's fast!
So this is Piercing Blood?!
Tsk!
Don't push yourself too hard.
You're exhausted, aren't you?
So what?
Is that any reason not to risk my life
for the younger brother right in front of me?
Just asking, but you two are strangers, right?
Worse than strangers. He nearly killed me once already.
First it was Todo.
Are you sure you aren't emitting dangerous pheromones or something?
Still, thanks to him, the fight has grown chaotic.
We're taking advantage of this.
Right.
I still have two cores, so I'll lead in the front.
If we all attack him together, it should at least create an opening.
We must do everything we can to steal back the Prison Realm.
Drumming—
Ice Formation:
Frost Calm!
An ice cursed technique?!
And one this high-level?!
If I move, I'll shatter my body!
Tsk!
Don't kill them.
I need messengers.
Is that any reason to leave them all alive?
A reverse cursed technique!
Their sorcery is on a different scale.
I want to go home!
This ice isn't enough!
Flowing Red Scale!
Then how much is?
Whose body do you think that is?!
I was the only one not frozen as solid!
Must have to do with Sukuna!
You're our ally, right?
No!
Huh?!
I'm your older brother.
Could you please take this seriously?!
Why don't you try saying it once, for starters?
Call me "Onii."
Tool Manipulation:
Wind Scythe!
Shit!
It's depressing that they parried it with their bare hands!
Itadori!
We're the only ones who can move right now!
We need to buy time for Utahime to finish her preparations!
Itadori Yuji
is the only messenger you need, right?!
Ice Formation: Icefall!
We're gonna die!
Long time no see,
Geto.
Could I get your answer to my question from back then?
What kind of woman is your type?
Tsukumo Yuki!
When one person's happiness conflicts with another person's happiness,
that's when unhappiness is born,
but when two people's unhappiness conflicts,
it usually only creates more unhappiness, you know?
Next time, Shibuya Incident: Gate, Close.
I just want to crawl into a warm bed and sleep.