My teach!
If it wasn't for him, I would've been
executed by now, so he's also...
The one who saved my life. Technically.
And it's not just me, there are many others who...
Don't know him all that well, to be honest.
What I can say for certain is that he is...
A dumbass.
A certified idiot.
Salmon.
But also...
Irresponsible. Egotistical.
And without a speck of doubt...
The strongest!
Hey, weed.
This is our third meeting, right?
And you still haven't learned your lesson.
I'll kill you first.
Come on, bring it.
What's wrong?
Didn't you guys tell me not to run away?
Did he just touch—
Ready for it?
He's only targeting Jogo.
Was he confusing us with his declaration earlier?
And not just that...
He has also deactivated his Limitless technique!
Using his technique in this crowded space
would require extreme precision.
Is he planning to stick to close combat
with just cursed energy manipulation?
In that case, I don't need to blend in with the crowd anymore.
I don't need to hold back on using my technique!
Don't deactivate Domain Extension, Hanami!
I heard this is your weak spot.
I knew it.
Domain Extension and innate techniques
can't be used at the same time.
The only reason I'm still alive is because
I was protecting myself with Domain Extension.
He's this strong with just physical attacks and
basic cursed energy manipulation!
Gojo Satoru, is there anything you're not capable of?!
Tch.
He's not a cursed spirit.
Must be one of the Death Painting Womb incarnations.
Annoying, but he'll have to wait.
Are you sure about this?
The more you try to neutralize my technique
with Domain Extension, the more I will reinforce it.
You think this asparagus here
has the energy left to handle that?
Gojo Satoru! I'll kill them all!
Hanami...
Next.
The Prison Realm is a living barrier—the remains of Genshin.
There is nothing that Prison Realm can't seal.
In that case, there must be some conditions to using it.
One minute.
What?
Once the Prison Realm's gate is opened,
the target must be in its four-meter
sealing range for one whole minute.
That's where you need to keep Gojo Satoru.
Hold up.
I will burn you alive.
Surely you didn't join forces just to
push that impossible task onto us, did you?
To keep that thing under
those conditions for one whole minute
even a thousand measly
human lives wouldn't be enough!
Things are getting a little heated here, Jogo.
Don't worry.
When I say one minute...
I won't let Hanami's death be in vain.
Blend into the crowd. Focus on hit-and-runs!
Choso!
If you don't help, I'll kill you with my own hands!
Yeah, yeah.
Not too close, not too far.
That's not gonna work for long, though.
People who can't see curses
are starting to move away from me.
As their numbers keep dwindling,
once there's enough space, I can catch Volcano Head.
I doubt I could trick them
by deactivating my technique again.
I've revealed my goal of
beating them to a pulp in close combat.
It'll be a problem if they unleash a
large-scale coordinated attack on the crowd.
I'm sorry. I won't be able to save everyone.
But in return...
I will make sure they're exorcised.
What's taking so long?!
It must have been twenty minutes by now!
Not even close.
Gojo Satoru is still completely composed.
We need him more on edge.
Hey, are you oka—
Everyone... into monsters... on the train...
I... I was told...
The train was full! Didn't need me!
He was here!
Damn it!
Everyone...
...on the train?
There are eight carriages on the incoming train.
Please stand behind the yellow line.
Mr. Gojo!
Please do not put your hands or head
beyond the platform door, or lean against them.
Train's here! Finally!
We can go home now!
It's here!
Hey!
Excuse me.
Let me through!
Ow!
Come on!
It's the train!
Outta my way! I'm gettin' in!
What're you doing?!
Can we go in?
No, wait!
What the hell are they thinking?
Jogo!
Man, the air smells so nice here.
Full of fear and dread!
We should totally keep a few humans alive.
We'll release them into the forest
and hunt them on the weekends!
Can I burn down the forest along with them?
Hanami would get upset over that.
Hanami is dead.
Seriously?
Whoa! I can't hit you for real!
Patchface!
The one Nanami and Yuji mentioned?!
Do you know what I find so disgusting about humans?
There's just too many of them!
There must be more of them above.
Blood Manipulation:
Convergence.
Idle Transfiguration:
Soul Multiplicity.
Supernova.
Body Repel.
Unlike Itadori Yuji, Gojo Satoru is
capable of making cold decisions.
I know he's willing to make sacrifices
if it means exorcising us.
But with the rising number of
humans killed and about to be killed,
how many sacrifices can he justify?
You have but one option right now:
Use your Infinite Void to kill us along with
every human here to save the ones outside the domain.
But you are incapable of doing that.
The only sacrifices you're willing to accept
are people killed by curses,
not people killed by Gojo Satoru.
Now, think and agonize.
Until you're on the edge!
No way!
Domain Expansion:
Infinite Void.
It was an all or nothing Domain Expansion of only 0.2 seconds.
The duration was decided by Gojo Satoru purely on instinct.
It was the amount of time he believed non-sorcerers could withstand Infinite Void
without suffering lasting effects.
During those 0.2 seconds,
roughly half a year's worth of information
flowed into the brains of non-sorcerers
and transfigured humans,
rendering every one of them unconscious on their feet.
In the aftermath, all the survivors from B5
were able to return to society two months later.
That's how precise his Infinite Void was.
That also meant the special-grade cursed spirits
could reawaken at any moment.
With the possibility of a counterattack in mind,
Gojo Satoru narrowed his targets to the transfigured humans.
Upon deactivation of the domain,
roughly 1,000 transfigured humans
unleashed upon B5 were annihilated in 299 seconds
at the hands of the strongest sorcerer
of the modern age.
Prison Realm: Gate, Open.
Don't worry.
When I say one minute...
'Sup,
Satoru.
Huh?
It's been a while.
A fake?
Some transformation technique?
No, it really is him!
It's one minute's worth of time in Gojo Satoru's mind.
Come now, Satoru. You shouldn't
lose yourself in thought in the midst of battle.
I can't sense any cursed energy.
I can't even move a muscle.
Is this game over?
So, who the hell are you?
I'm Geto Suguru, of course.
Don't you remember me? How sad.
Whether it's your body or your cursed energy,
my Six Eyes tell me you're Geto Suguru.
But...
My soul denies it!
Now, give me a straight answer!
Who the hell are you?!
Creepy.
How could you tell?
That is my technique, you see.
I can hop between bodies
by replacing its brain with myself.
It also lets me use the body's
innate techniques, of course.
I needed his Curse Manipulation and this exact situation.
Back then, you didn't have Ieiri Shoko
handle the disposal of Geto Suguru's body, did you?
That was an odd time for you to show consideration.
Thanks to that, I was able to obtain this body with ease.
You needn't worry. The seal will be broken eventually.
In a hundred... no, maybe a thousand years from now?
You're just too strong.
And you're in the way of my plans.
Aren't you forgetting something?
Before it was killed by me, who was it that
beat the crap out of that body?
Okkotsu Yuta, huh?
I really don't get what everyone sees in that boy.
His ability to copy techniques unconditionally
as well as his boundless cursed energy
are both merely a result of the Binding Vow that
links him with the soul of his beloved.
Sorry to say this, but Okkotsu Yuta
will never be you.
Goodnight, Gojo Satoru.
We'll meet again in the new world.
What the—
What's the matter?
There's... something on my ear.
Can you hear me, Itadori Yuji?
There's no time.
Listen carefully, I'll only say this once.
Gojo Satoru has been sealed.
What do you think of skin care?
What? You're asking me that? Not that I mind.
I use all kinds of products, but like, it's just genetics.
I'm sure those with pale, smooth skin like Mr. Gojo
would say, "I don't really do anything."
Next time, Pandemonium.
So what do you actually do?
I don't really do anything.
Grr!