I think I'll go see a movie.
What about you, Kugisaki?
It's still early. I'll go shopping or something.
You all have so much energy.
I'm going home, then.
Take care.
Finally done.
I'm going to the movies. What about you?
What are you seeing?
Human Earthworm 4.
Who'd ever go see that?
I haven't even seen 1, 2, or 3.
I think you'd be fine jumping in on 4.
This time, the mad scientist from the first one,
Dr. Richter, is making his long-awaited reappearance!
Stop! Let me go!
And the hybrid human-earthworm fusion born from the doctor's experiments
is going to give rise to an enhanced Human Earthworm!
What the hell? That's so gross.
The poor Human Earthworm, who barely escaped from Dr. Richter with its life,
finally wanders into a campground where a group of college students are,
and that's when the story really kicks off.
So, one of the people in that group is a kind woman who's an animal rights proponent,
and the Human Earthworm falls in love with her.
I'm no longer human.
You're more human than anyone else.
It's a monster! Kill it!
Kevin, stop!
If we kill him, then we're the monsters!
Papa.
Papa?
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
So the theme is actually love!
I don't want see some wormo man, regardless of the theme.
It's "Human Earthworm."
It doesn't matter.
I'm going shopping, okay?
Want to come with?
I just said I'm going to the movies.
Okay. Later, then.
Special-grade is a rank reserved for those sorcerers who are exceptional.
In my opinion, first-grade is the true rank for the sorcerers
who will lead other sorcerers and jujutsu society.
They must stand above comparison to semi-first- grades in terms of peril, secrecy, and salary.
Now, with that in mind, what did you just say?
Maki Zenin, Panda...
...Megumi Fushiguro, Nobara Kugisaki, and my brother, Yuji Itadori.
On my name as Aoi Todo...
And on my name as Mei Mei...
I recommend those five for first-grade sorcerer.
Those who are recommended by at least two first-grades
must carry out missions under an active first-grade,
or first-grade equivalent sorcerer.
Then, if they are deemed fit, they will be promoted to semi-first-grade
and proceed to be assigned first-grade missions on their own.
Following the results of those missions,
they either will or won't officially become first-grade sorcerers.
My brother will certainly accept the recommendation.
With Sukuna still uncooperative,
he'll need to go on more dangerous missions
to raise his chances of finding more fingers.
You understand what that means, right, Ms. Mei?
What that means? That's everything, Mr. Todo.
A bright future...
It means a bright future where Aoi Todo and Yuji Itadori
face missions together lies ahead of us!
No...
You don't have to say it.
There's no guarantee I'll be the first-grade sorcerer assigned to accompany him.
That's what you wanted to say, right?
But I'm certain of this!
It's as certain as apples falling from a tree!
The two of us are drawn together!
Yes, it truly is destiny!
No, I mean...
The sorcerers who recommended him can't be assigned to accompany him.
Since we're the two that recommended Itadori,
someone else will have to accompany him.
Thanks for today.
I'll be leaving now, Mr. Todo.
Um, excuse me.
You were with Itadori earlier, right?
Huh?
Welcome!
This is what I looked like at our middle school graduation ceremony.
Huh?! Seriously?! That was only six months ago!
What happened to you?!
Well, I've grown about 15 centimeters since then.
That combined with the stress of moving to Tokyo and changing environments...
Wow...
You're a real Kuroko Sato.
That's Itadori.
On graduation day, I worked up the courage to ask for a photo with him.
I actually wanted to ask for his phone number,
but it was already decided that we would be moving to Tokyo...
So when I saw Itadori earlier,
I thought maybe with how I look now, I might...
Wait... Yuko, you mean...
It's like that, right?
Yes! It's like that!
Hey, Ijichi.
Is Fushiguro still riding with you?
I sent you the URL for the restaurant I'm at.
Could you turn around and bring him here?
Thanks! See ya soon!
Someone who knows Itadori well is on his way here now.
Um...
We'll talk to him about it first.
If you're also interested in Itadori...
No.
Even if hell froze over and danced the lambada...
My chest just felt weird.
Did my heart skip a beat?
Yo, what's the big idea?
Hey, Fushiguro!
Does Itadori have a girlfriend?
Huh?
This is Yuko Ozawa.
She's actually blah, blah, blah.
So it's like that?!
Yeah, it's like that!
He definitely doesn't have a girlfriend.
Your basis for that?
When he suddenly had to transfer to Tokyo, he didn't seem particularly upset about it.
He also has a pinup poster hanging in his room.
Anyone with a girlfriend wouldn't have something like that hanging up, right?
Because she'd hate it.
Are you the type to drink coffee black only when women around so you can show off?
Stop it, okay?
You called me out here to ask me about this, right?
And I always drink it black.
Um, by the way, do you know what his type is?
Oh...
He mentioned he likes tall girls.
You have a shot!
I'll summon Itadori!
You're okay with that, right, Yuko?!
Yes!
That was curt.
Really?
Huh? Fushiguro is here, too?
That was fast!
Oh, shoot.
What's that?
I haven't told Itadori about Yuko!
Finding a money exchange was a pain, so I traded in for prizes instead.
He definitely won't recognize who she is after she changed so much!
Who are you?
That's the #1 line you never want to hear when reuniting with the person you adore!
Itadori!
This girl is—
Huh?
You're Ozawa.
What are you doing here?
What a coincidence.
Okay, so which girl in our class do you like, Itadori?
None of them, really.
If you had to pick! If you had to!
Huh?
If I had to pick, then, Ozawa.
No way, man. She's fat.
I guess?
But the way she eats and her handwriting and stuff are really pretty.
Don't you agree it's hard to eat fish?!
I thought you said you liked tall girls with big butts?
That's its own thing!
It's easy for girls to get fat.
I started off fat,
but even I don't have interest in choosing someone who won't choose me.
Itadori was looking at a side of me I wasn't aware of.
I hated all the boys other than Itadori.
But...
"Maybe with how I look now, I might..."
I'm living by the same standards as the people I hate.
Later.
See you tomorrow.
See you later.
Was that really okay?
They could have at least exchanged numbers.
She exchanged hers with me,
so yeah, it'll be fine.
More importantly, Fushiguro,
I've finally realized my own feelings.
Huh?
The thought that Itadori might land a girlfriend
before I get a boyfriend pisses me off.
That so?
Sorry for the wait.
Walk behind me.
Huh? What's this?
What are you talking about?
Here.
Oh? Thanks!
Huh? Huh? What's this?
While you're at it, while you're at it.
While I'm at it?
You'd feel bad making a lady carry them, right?
Sure.
Oh, shoot!
The movie's starting!
Hey, let's go!
Come on, come on, come on. Here, here.
Huh?! Hold up!
Don't take mine with you!
There's no way I'm watching some wormo man!
You want some popcorn, too, Fushiguro?!
You like caramel flavoring, right?!
Don't just advance the conversation assuming we're going to watch wormo man.
I told you all it's Human Earthworm 4!
Impossible!
Working with a curse user is one thing,
but cursed spirits?!
Yet, lately, cursed spirits of that level have been popping up everywhere.
The person in question may think they're only working with curse users, though.
I want to leave the investigation of Kyoto up to you, Utahime.
This way.
You've heard from Gojo about the person leaking intel, right?
Yes.
There's probably two or more people in contact with the curse users.
One would be a higher-up, well above the principal.
I won't be able to do anything about that one.
The other would be someone passing the information up to that higher-up.
That one is our current target.
They're only a suspect at this point,
so we'll capture and then interrogate them.
So who from Kyoto is it?
Oh?!
That's why you asked those of us from Tokyo, right?
Kugisaki, you're incredible.
The mole is—
Mechamaru!
Oh, there you are.
Today's the last day to turn in your notebook.
Mechamaru?
Sorry, Miwa.
I'm going to sleep for a bit.
Please take the notebook from my desk.
Sleep? It's still only evening?
Jeez!
He really did go to sleep.
I wonder where the real Mechamaru actually is.
Mechamaru's real body,
Kokichi Muta, is in the basement here.
Now, it's not like he's suspicious.
It's more that everyone else wasn't.
So the process of elimination leaves us with Mechamaru.
Mechamaru's technique is puppet manipulation.
Though, thanks to his Heavenly Pact,
the range he can manipulate puppets in extends throughout all of Japan.
If he has any unregistered puppets,
then he could do the work of a mole as much as he wanted.
Really?
That guy stood out a lot to me.
Even if the puppet was the size of a fly or a mosquito?
I see.
So those are options, too, huh?
We're here.
They've arrived?
Uh...
He got us.
Though, on the other hand...
Now we're certain it's Mechamaru.
You're late.
I thought you forgot about me.
We wouldn't make a blunder like that.
You're already personally familiar with the terrifying nature of a pact, right?
He always smells moldy and I hate it.
We're enemies, too, so let's just kill him quick.
You can't do that yet, Mahito.
He agreed to cooperate with us and provide us information.
In exchange,
we agreed to use your Idle Transfiguration to fix his body.
That's the pact we all forged, remember?
Killing him comes after fixing him.
I wanted him to do some work for us in Shibuya, too,
so that's a shame.
"We won't lay a hand on the people from the Kyoto school."
You're the ones who broke our pact first.
Hanami's the one who did that.
You shouldn't lash out at the wrong people.
I have no intention of getting into a debate with cursed spirits.
Hurry up and fix me, scumbag.
Maybe I'll get carried away and turn him into a caterpillar.
Mahito.
Pacts forged with others are very different from pacts placed upon oneself.
The first aspect of that is the uncertain nature of the penalty.
When you break a pact with yourself, whatever you gained...
the improvement to your own ability is lost,
but this time you can't break it.
If you break this pact,
then we have no idea when, or what kind of disaster will befall us.
Yeah, yeah.
You're lower than a scumbag, so be grateful.
Idle Transfiguration.
Hmph.
No fun at all.
Celebrate a bit more.
I'll do that after I'm finished here.
I suppose that's true.
Well, shall we get started?
Want my help?
Stop it.
He's my toy.
There!
Hmph!
He escaped?
Well, it's not like he needs to kill us.
How boring.
I wanted to have a match, not go hunting, you know.
That's more like it!
So you've been making something like this in secret?
Guess you weren't a shut-in just for show.
He's inside it, right?
He wouldn't want me to touch him after all.
The cockpit...
The seat of his soul...
is the head!
Expansion rate normal.
Perception feedback severed.
Tsk.
They lowered a Veil.
Must be Geto.
It's not just attempting to trap me inside.
It's cutting off signal, too.
This won't be as easy as it was for Satoru Gojo.
That's right, my victory condition is Satoru Gojo.
I have to use any means necessary to get in contact with Satoru Gojo,
and tell him about the Shibuya plot.
Then I'll have him protect me.
However, even if I want to focus on Geto, the one who lowered this Veil,
Mahito, is too dangerous to ignore.
I'll have to exorcise him first.
Go ahead, don't mind me.
I'm still at a disadvantage.
But I have a chance to win.
I've seen it all.
I have all the time I was bound.
All the cursed energy I gained from that time.
I won't hold anything back.
Charge, 1 year!
Burn him, Mechamaru!
Ultra Cannon!
I decided I would never tell anyone about the things I truly want to keep secret
when I wrote out what type of boy I like in my profile
book during elementary school and had everyone find out.
Next Episode, Evening Festival!
What did you write down?
Mittermeyer.
He does seem like he'd be fast.