I knew.
I knew he was stronger.
But to think it was to this extent!
He's this fast without any cursed energy?
He must be the perfected form of Maki.
Focus!
Thanks to Inumaki, all the normal people
and transfigured humans are out of the way.
Visualize it!
Visualize how to beat this guy!
Visualize winning!
Fleeing Hares!
That sensation was Sukuna's fingers!
What the hell is happening here in Shibuya?!
He charged through on pure instinct!
Shit! I no longer have the cursed energy to use Domain Expansion, either!
Kusakabe, aren't we done with the interiors yet?
They might still be in the Veil,
but thanks to Toge, everyone's been evacuated,
so let's head to Satoru.
How do we get to floor B5 from here?
Toge said the news about him being sealed is real, so let's hurry!
Gojo this, Gojo that.
Gojo isn't the only person in the world!
Who knows who might be trembling in a nook of Shibuya right this very instant?
Imagine if it were some young elementary school girls.
How would you feel if we overlooked them?
It wouldn't be an exaggeration to say we were
responsible for snuffing out such a bright future!
M-Maybe you're right.
If you understand, then get to scouring every building, every floor,
and behind all the toilets, you dumbass!
This is bad.
I'm running out of room for excuses.
I definitely don't want to go near floor B5.
I'd much prefer to wander around like this and waste time.
Because I don't want to die!
If Panda knew how to get there, he'd run off for floor B5 on his own.
I want to avoid that, too!
Because I don't want to be left here alone right now!
He might be a panda, but he has more of a human heart than I do.
But because he's a panda, he has no sense of his surroundings here in Shibuya.
He hasn't even noticed that we're already super close to floor B5.
I'll go look over there!
Yeah, be thorough about it!
Maybe I'll pretend to be lost in the station next.
This huge bundle of cursed energy keeps appearing
and disappearing from the culprits who sealed Gojo.
No way I'm touching that. That would be stupid.
You're sorcerers from Jujutsu Tech, right?
Surrender.
I don't want to kill sorcerers if I don't have to.
Panda.
I count three behind him, probably more in hiding.
I don't want to get murdered, either, but I can't just roll over and say yes.
So why don't we have a chat?
A nice, long one.
The longer this goes, the worse off I am!
I'll have to risk a short, decisive battle!
The one advantage I do have...
Principal. I have your cursed corpses with me, so I'll be fine on my own.
You know that's not enough.
The moment they learn about this place, they'll target it.
Now even Satoru is capable of healing others with his reverse cursed technique.
Ino and Ijichi would both be dead if you weren't here.
That was thanks to your quick judgment, Principal.
If we'd waited for Nanami to call for me, we wouldn't have made it in time.
Allowing Nanami to operate freely has been a major boon.
I thought you had quit smoking?
I'm recalling the days when I was a student for a bit.
...is that Ieiri is close by!
So it's okay to push my body further than I should!
I just need to settle this with only injuries she can heal!
I've narrowed down his paths!
But his speed is on par with Sukuna from that time.
Don't try to follow him by sight! Just focus on the timing!
If I mess up the timing, I'm dead.
If I mess up the timing,
I'm dead!
Damn it!
You know my brat?
He's totally got it all.
I wouldn't mind giving him to you once his technique becomes clear at age five or six.
Depending on how much you'll pay, of course.
If he has the hereditary technique, I'll take eight,
and I'll take seven for anything else.
Hah!
If he has the hereditary technique, I'll pay you ten.
Even if that place was a trash dump to me,
it should be much better for him since he has the talent.
Not that I care anymore.
Not that I care at all.
Please take care of Megumi.
Hey, you.
What's your name?
Fushiguro?
It's not Zenin?
I'm glad.
What the hell was that about?
Enough worrying about that now.
I need to make haste to Ieiri.
No, I should make sure Maki and the others are safe first...
See, see? This is it!
This is what I'm suited to!
Cooperate with that thing?
You mean for the sake of reclaiming Master Geto's body, right?
No.
The true identity and goals of that impostor may be unclear,
but once the world is thrown into chaos,
those non-sorcerer monkeys will be the ones paying the price.
Being strong will be necessary for survival.
The monkeys will be culled,
sorcerers will propagate,
and cursed spirits will disappear.
That is the world Master Geto longed for.
That's why we'll cooperate.
I won't concern myself with the body.
That's what it means to inherit his ambition.
Don't go making this all mixed up and complicated.
I'm telling you I won't stay quiet while
the man I loved is being manipulated like a zombie!
Master Geto's story is finished.
I won't let anyone taint that!
Grow up already, Nanako.
If you start going on
about grown-ups and children, this conversation's over!
Hey!
Both of you, settle down.
The one thing Suguru would want least of all is for us to hurt each other.
Neither of you is wrong here.
So let's agree this is where we part ways.
We can each do as we please.
What'll you do, Larue?
I won't take either side.
Same as Miguel.
I just wanted to make Suguru king, after all.
But all of you, remember this.
We're a family.
Someday, somewhere, we'll all share a meal together again.
We are the ones carrying on the will of Master Geto.
If you're with Jujutsu Tech,
then nothing else needs to be said.
Will you surrender or not?
I hate indecisive men.
I'm a panda, so that doesn't apply to me.
Their chat was too short, damn it!
Still, though...
With a group on this level?
It's too perfect.
I can take plenty of time just fending them off and dragging this out.
New Shadow Style Iai, Evening Moon.
So that's your answer?
This is your reward for the fingers. Come at me.
If you manage to land even a single blow on me,
I'll work under you all.
For starters, how about I slaughter every human in Shibuya?
Except for one.
Is that all you've got...
Not yet!
...cursed spirit?!
Geto, how strong would you say I am in terms of Sukuna's fingers?
A generous estimation would be about eight or nine fingers.
I knew.
I knew he was stronger.
I knew there was a gap in our strength.
But to think it was to this extent!
The moonlight's shining all the way through.
It's helping me see your pathetic state more clearly.
Come on, now. Keep trying.
I'll play along with you again and again until I tire of this.
It's dangerous to remain here any longer!
Time to run!
Where are you going?!
Listen, you!
Listen up, you curse users!
I don't know why, but a couple of special-grades are fighting each other!
A bunch of elephants are now tap-dancing on top of ants!
And just to be clear, we're the ants!
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry!
Supreme Art:
Meteor!
New Shadow Style:
Quick Draw!
Panda!
Let's hurry up and run!
You won't.
I hereby forbid every person in a 100-meter radius from moving until I say "now."
And of course, I'll kill anyone who violates that rule.
Not yet.
Still not yet.
Now!
Even Sukuna shouldn't escape that unharmed.
If it had hit.
Why won't you use your domain?
I know I can't win a tug-of-war between domains.
Because that's how it went with Gojo Satoru?
That's the epitome of a loser's spirit.
Though you have managed to pique my interest.
So I'll fight you with your own specialty.
■, Fuga (Open).
Those are...
flames?!
I thought Sukuna's technique was severing and slicing...
Oh? I thought it was well-known,
but I suppose you wouldn't know, cursed spirit.
Don't worry. I won't do anything petty like revealing my technique.
Arm yourself.
Let's have a contest of firepower.
I'm sorry, Hanami, Dagon.
There's still Mahito.
Humans fear and loathe death.
Yet the ones standing behind that are also humans.
To humans, death is a mirror.
And Mahito is that mirror.
Mahito will continue to grow stronger still.
That's why you placed him at the top of our ranks, right?
We'll no longer be the same as we are now once we're reborn again.
Yet even so, I'll eagerly await the day we meet again.
We are the true humans.
What's this now?
You wanted to become human?
Yeah, I know.
You don't want to actually be human. You want their position.
Is that about right?
Even when I understand it, that's so dumb.
Packs of humans. Packs of curses.
All of you get together and measure your worth against each other,
driving all of you to grow weaker and stunted.
You should have burnt everything down.
Burnt everything around you, without calculations or plots.
Casting aside race, future, everything... until you finally reached Gojo Satoru.
That hunger to seize your ideals
is what you were lacking.
Maybe you're right.
Still, you managed to entertain me a bit.
I fought humans, sorcerers, and cursed spirits a thousand years ago,
and you were still one of the better ones I fought.
Be proud.
You were strong.
What is this?
Good question.
I wouldn't know that.
Who are you?
I've come to welcome you,
Sukuna-sama.
Uraume!
It's been a long time.
Oh, fuck you!
Damn it!
Wake up, you shitty sorcerer!
Lately I see the Internet talking about Mentos and soda, but is it really true?
Why do you ask?
I'm pretty sure I happened to eat a Mentos while drinking soda at least once when I was kid.
The fact that I don't remember it means those videos must be fakes!
Got it! Eat up!
Next time, Thunderclap, Part 2.
See you next week!