Do you remember
the ways to rid cursed spirits from our world?
Regardless of which method is pursued,
it means advancing humanity to the next stage.
Now, I need to buy time for Larue to act.
Humanity's next stage is
freeing itself from cursed energy.
No. It's optimizing cursed energy.
Uh, I don't get it, either.
I thought you already gave on your plan twelve years ago, when Zenin Toji died.
I was talking to Geto, you know.
Well, whatever.
I went back to my original idea.
Besides, there's a big hole in your optimization plan.
Extremely few sorcerers and cursed spirits emerge in other countries compared to Japan.
So Tengen's barriers should be indispensable to your optimization plan.
Using Tengen to optimize cursed energy would mean
only the humans of this nation would become sorcerers.
Japan would practically have a monopoly on cursed energy.
Other nations, especially that superpower, wouldn't stand by and allow that.
Flesh-and-blood humans would become an energy source.
It's easy enough to imagine what misfortune that would bring.
That's a world far removed from the ideals I pursue.
So what?
For one thing, our objectives are different.
I don't desire a world without cursed spirits
or any sort of idyllic peace.
Non-sorcerers, sorcerers, cursed spirits...
Those are all possibilities
for the shape of cursed energy that is mankind.
Though that shouldn't be anywhere near the full extent.
I tried to give rise
to other possibilities for mankind on my own.
But that didn't work out.
Everything that I created myself
was limited by the bounds of my own potential.
The answer was always glimmering darkly within chaos.
Do you understand?
What I should have created
was chaos that went beyond my own control.
I've already finished extracting the technique.
There was a cursed spirit called Mahito, right?!
The one with the technique that let it interfere with souls!
That guy absorbed it earlier.
Seriously?!
Idle Transfiguration.
Tengen's barrier? No, this is...
Remote activation of a cursed technique?!
You have my thanks, Itadori Yuji.
A cursed spirit's mastery of their technique ceases to progress
from the moment they're absorbed by Cursed Spirit Manipulation.
Mahito truly matured through his fight with you.
To be honest, I wanted to have Jogo, as well, but no matter.
What did you do?
I remotely activated Idle Transfiguration on
two types of non-sorcerers that I marked ahead of time.
One type was people whom I had absorb cursed objects like Itadori Yuji did,
and the other was people like Junpei Yoshino who have cursed techniques,
but whose brains were structured like non-sorcerers.
Now I've adjusted their brains to match those of sorcerers.
For the former, I gave them the strength to be vessels,
and the latter have obtained the ability to activate their techniques.
And now...
I've released the seal on those cursed objects.
Some of them have been in a deep sleep
after being exposed to my cursed energy when I marked them,
but they'll soon awaken.
So, starting now,
I'll have them kill each other in order to deepen their understanding of cursed energy.
I've carefully hand-picked these people and cursed objects.
Think of it as unleashing a thousand malevolent Itadori Yujis.
A thousand?
That's conservative.
You're also underestimating human rationality.
Do you think people will start
killing each other just because they were granted power?
There's an order to everything.
I certainly didn't cut corners like that when making my preparations.
Your questions are starting to become shallow.
He's pissing me off, so let's all beat him up together!
I can't move right now, though...
What's the matter, Uraume?
I regenerated my body with a reverse cursed technique...
This is...
Poison?!
My blood got mixed with yours through Piercing Blood.
Of course it is.
Wait, we're not getting cover from Mai.
They might still have more allies over there.
My ally is protecting Aoi, the girl with the gun, and that suit.
They don't belong here.
Can you move?
Yeah.
I can adjust my body heat.
No problems here.
I'm so done.
We were in the middle of our talk.
The cursed objects that I distributed are what's left of the sorcerers
I've been secretly making pacts with for a thousand years.
Of course, I forged my pacts with more than just sorcerers,
though my pacts with those were annulled when I obtained this body.
You don't mean...
This is the world of the future.
See you later, Itadori Yuji.
Gojo!
I have high expectations for you.
Are you listening, Sukuna?
It's starting once again.
The world of Heian, the golden age of jujutsu!
The following footage was recorded by our crew, who happened to be on-site
reporting on a different matter at the time of the incident in Tokyo the other day.
Please have a look.
Uh, it's been about ten minutes since the blackout, I think?
It's been a while, and the blackout continues.
Something really crazy is going on.
Sure it's not fake news?
We still cannot contact the station, so the cause remains unknown,
All the news is covering this, though.
Hmm... Well, I'll be getting home late today, so have a frozen dinner.
and we have practically no idea what's going on.
Sure.
All 23 wards are nearly wiped out.
The safety of the Prime Minister's office,
including the Chief Cabinet Secretary, remains uncertain.
It's a political void!
A literal hole!
No matter how low we estimate it,
we need to make a plan to evacuate at least five million citizens.
Love hotels, campgrounds, ghost towns...
Use whatever you can, as long as it has the bare minimum infrastructure.
More importantly, how are we supposed to explain this to the residents?
There's no point announcing anything when we don't know the cause!
Also, the government has yet to make an announcement.
Was this simply the malfunction of a substation?
Was it terrorism?
Or perhaps... it was a natural disaster, like an earthquake?
Too many conspiracy theorists are crawling out.
Either way, the cause remains unclear,
Listen, would you put your phone away and come help me here?
and we're being forced to wait while they uncover it.
Very well.
All we can firmly declare safe are portions of
Okutama, Oume City, Akiruno City, Hachioji City,
Machida City, and various islands.
For now, you mean.
The number of cursed spirits unleashed is no less than ten million.
You want to enact an evacuation order on every ward of the entire city?
Afterward, we declare the wards forbidden to entry.
Make it a real uninhabited zone.
More importantly, what about our announcement?
Who's making it?
Less "who" and more "how" to make it.
We still can't get a hold of the deputy secretary?
No, we can't.
I haven't heard anything from his secretary, either.
What should we do?
Now, now, the upper brass will figure that out.
For now, we need to establish contact with each ministry.
The low yen ain't stopping.
That was at least good for exports, right?
The Japanese Business Federation has lost it?
They won't be doing any lobbying if everyone's dead.
Move the Prime Minister to Osaka!
At this rate, there'll be a massive outbreak of cursed spirits everywhere!
Most jujutsu sorcerers are already assigned to protecting evacuees in the city!
And that outbreak is coming now!
With a power vacuum of this scale,
we may see military intervention from other nations.
Yes. Huh?
Oh, no.
Yes.
I understand.
They're going to publicly announce the existence of cursed spirits.
Huh?!
They're going public with cursed spirits?!
Are they seriously suggesting that?!
Apparently, they intend to announce that cursed spirits only arise in Tokyo.
So the goal is to direct the populace's leaking cursed energy to Tokyo
and limit the outbreak of cursed spirits to there, huh?
This is why I recommended Itami as a potential relocation site after Kansai Airport was built!
Maybe it's better this way?
They wouldn't have reached this decision if Kasumigaseki was functioning.
Um, once again, we're sharing the latest.
The blackout still continues as before,
and we're unable to contact anyone.
There's been no official announcement, either, so the cause remains unknown.
The question is, how long will this last—hmm?
What?  What is that?!
Hey!
Huh? What is this?
A movie?
The barrier centered around the Imperial Palace that was erected in the Meiji era,
and the barrier centered directly above the Tombs of the Star Corridor,
which was a proposed site for the relocation of Tokyo in the Bakumatsu era,
will be forcibly expanded out to the borders of the prefecture.
Come.
It's dangerous here.
I have a warm bath.
I can sing songs, too.
What about my mom?
Your mother, father,
older sister, younger brother, and teacher are all here.
I don't have a younger brother.
And I hate my teacher.
Are you okay?
Need a drink?
Please?
Sorry.
Did I scare you?
Are you hurt?
Were you with anyone?
Like your mom or dad?
I don't know.
It's all commercial buildings here,
so I guess she's not from around here?
Did you walk a lot?
I see. You worked hard.
You can see them, huh?
That's bad, Rika.
Don't overdo it.
I'm sorry. I hesitated.
I thought I should sit back and watch,
and give him room to work, since the situation had already progressed so far.
Have you realized yet?
I'm not really on your side.
I'm just a humble beauty who wants to eradicate cursed spirits from the world.
It might not be much of an apology,
but my allies and I will take responsibility for delivering the kids who were there.
It's high time I confronted Tengen, too.
What will you do?
Good work, Okkotsu.
You don't really intend to thank me,
so let's just get to the point.
Now you understand that I'll obey your orders, right?
No amount of killing cursed spirits will prove anything.
Then forge a pact or whatever you need to.
It doesn't matter that he's one of Gojo's students.
He cut off Inumaki's arms in Shibuya.
So I will kill Itadori Yuji.