Things were busy that summer.
Perhaps due to all those frequent disasters last year.
Curses were springing up like maggots.
Exorcise. Consume.
Over and over.
Exorcise.
Consume.
It's a taste nobody knows.
The taste of a curse.
Like swallowing a rag used to wipe up shit and vomit.
Exorcise.
Consume.
What I witnessed was nothing out of the ordinary.
A hideous evil known to everyone.
Despite knowing that, I still chose to be
a sorcerer who saves others.
That's what I've been telling myself ever since that day.
Ever since that day.
This building
belonged to the president of a company that ran
a chain of barbecue restaurants in the area.
However, his business suffered a devastating blow
due to the mad cow disease outbreak last July.
Burdened by huge debts,
he committed suicide with his family.
Since then, the mansion has become
a well-known haunted location.
From local school kids to college students
from outside, and even part-timers,
many visit it as a test of courage,
and many of them go missing.
As rumors continued to multiply,
the damage must have kept on escalating.
Rumors around haunted locations and such
do tend to spread rather quickly.
It's unbelievable how fast word gets around
these days thanks to the Internet.
All this just means more work for us sorcerers.
Additionally, three elementary school kids
went missing on their way home.
Their friends, families, or the police
must be out looking for them.
If they get to the mansion, there's a good chance
they might end up as victims themselves.
We have to sever the root
of the problem as soon as possible.
HQ seems to have the same idea.
That's why they sent me along to investigate.
It must be important
if they're willing to pay my fees.
Are you extorting them again?
You make it sound so bad.
It's called negotiation.
We're here.
Let's go, then.
Emerge from the darkness that is darker than black.
Purify that which—
A Veil won't be necessary.
Really?
I don't sense the presence of any curses here.
There's a very good chance that
it's inside the building.
You can cast the Veil later
if we end up attacking it from outside.
It's unlocked.
Seems like something's blocking the door.
What is all this?
Miss Mei.
It's here.
Its presence is all around us.
Let's get to work.
I don't need that, but I'm guessing you do.
Thank you.
All right.
This place is huge!
Oh, it still has electricity.
Let's take a quick look around the building first.
I'll take this floor. You take the second.
Huh? All by myself?
Is there a problem with that?
N-No, i-it's fine.
Off you go, then.
Okay.
This is the last one.
You could be the next big Scream Queen.
Jeez! Please don't startle me like that!
You got startled all on your own.
Are you done exploring the first floor?
This is the first floor.
Come again?
I was walking down the first floor hallway.
What? But...
I know I entered a room at the end of the hallway...
Boxes of snacks.
Bags of chips.
Juice cans.
Backpack.
Sweatshirt.
I've seen these three times by now.
Did you notice these marks?
I made them on my way through here.
It would seem that we're
already inside the belly of the beast.
No way...
For real?
How long is this hallway?
We've been moving for thirty minutes, so about four kilometers so far.
It's not an innate domain, is it?
It's not.
Those are manifestations of one's mindscape.
Any other ideas?
This must be a barrier.
Correct.
The victims were most likely trapped here too,
and eventually killed by the curse.
Considering it's using techniques like this,
the curse itself should be weak.
If we can just escape this barrier...
Time for a quiz.
How would you break this, Utahime?
This hallway is repeating itself.
At first...
I thought it was like this.
Bold of you to touch them.
I assumed it was shaped like a donut.
But we passed by four of the marks you made, right?
When I counted how many steps apart they were, I got...
122,
203,
157,
and 270 steps.
So the spacing between marks was random.
Interesting.
The interval between repetitions isn't consistent.
So I think... it must be something like this.
The barrier is patching spaces together.
I think if we both run down the hallway
at top speed, then at some point...
It'll break.
Close. Ninety points.
D'oh.
What did I miss?
Don't you think it would be more effective
if we ran in opposite directions?
I get it!
If my patching theory is correct,
running in opposite directions would make it harder
for the curse to hold the barrier together.
Once we have an opening, we might be able to escape!
One hundred points.
It's settled, then.
If this works, I'll be expecting a promotion.
How much do you have in savings?
What?
Never mind. I'll think about it.
Right!
Ready.
Set.
Go!
It worked!
Wait, wha—
I'm here to save your ass, Utahime.
You cryin'?
I'm not crying!
Respect your seniors!
If I was crying, would you console me?
I would certainly appreciate that.
Nah, I know you wouldn't cry, Miss Mei.
You're strong.
You think?
Gojo! You listen here!
I don't need your hel—
Don't swallow it.
I'll consume it later.
Satoru, it's not nice to pick on the weak.
What kinda idiot picks on the strong?
You're the one who is picking on her, Geto.
You don't even know it.
Oops.
Utahime!
Are you okay?
Shoko!
We hadn't heard from you for two whole days. I was worried.
Shoko! Don't turn out like those two, okay?!
No way I'll become trash like them.
Look at the trash where Utahime just walked by!
Shut up.
Wait, two days?
Ah, was it one of those barriers
that messes with your perception of time?
They're rare, but they do pop up
every now and then.
The whole situation did seem odd
since Miss Mei was with you.
That seems to be the case.
Something the matter?
Oh, I just realized that I technically worked for two days.
Maybe I should ask for additional compensation.
She's planning another extortion...
Back to the topic, you three.
Where is the Veil?
Next up is the explosion that occurred yesterday
in Hamamatsu, Shizuoka.
The explosion was caused due to degradation of gas pipes.
One of you told the assistant supervisor that you'd
cast the Veil yourself and left them behind.
Our reporter on the scene...
And then you forgot to do it.
Who was it?
Teach!
We're better than pointing fingers at each other!
So it was you, Satoru.
Is a Veil even necessary in the first place?
Does it even matter if normies see us?
It's not like they can see curses or
cursed techniques, anyway.
Of course it matters.
The primary factor preventing an outbreak
of curses is the citizens' peace of mind.
That's why we have to conceal the
threats they can't see as far as possible.
And that's not all—
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
Looking out for the weak is a pain in the ass, honestly.
Survival of the weakest.
That's the ideal form society should take.
Help the weak and keep the strong in check.
Listen carefully, Satoru.
Sorcerers exist to protect non-sorcerers.
Is that your moral argument? I hate moral arguments.
Excuse me?
Assigning responsibilities to the strong
in the name of some cause is what weak people do.
Get off your high horse and
quit spouting that feel-good bullshit.
Blegh.
I'm outta here.
Why don't we take this outside, Satoru?
You feeling lonely?
Go by yourself.
How long are you going to keep fooling around?
And where's Shoko?
Who knows?
Maybe the bathroom?
Whatever.
I'm going to have you two go on a mission together.
What's with the faces?
It's nothing.
I honestly think it's too important
to be assigned to you guys,
but Master Tengen asked for you specifically.
Your mission has two goals.
Master Tengen has found a compatible Star Plasma Vessel.
You are to escort that girl and erase her.
Escort a brat and erase her?
That's right.
Has he finally gone senile?
It's spring. He'll become the principal soon.
It must be getting to his head.
Jokes aside, though—
I'll be the one to decide if I let that off as a joke.
Is this about resetting Master Tengen's technique?
What's that?
What?
Master Tengen has the technique of Immortality,
but that doesn't grant him eternal youth.
It wouldn't be an issue if all he did was get older,
but after he ages to a certain point,
the technique will begin to rewrite his body.
Evolution.
He'll cease to be human and
become a higher form of existence.
What's wrong with that? Sounds cool.
According to Master Tengen,
those who reach that state of being have no will.
It means Master Tengen
would cease to be Master Tengen.
The jujutsu schools, the pillars of jujutsu society,
and the many barrier techniques of assistant supervisors
are all being strengthened by Master Tengen.
Without the aid of his power, we could
hardly maintain security or clean up after missions.
In the worst-case scenario,
Master Tengen could even become a threat to mankind.
That's why, every five hundred years,
he finds the Star Plasma Vessel—someone
who is compatible with him—and assimilates them,
overwriting his body's information.
By renewing his body, he resets his technique
back to the start to avoid evolution.
I get it.
So becoming MetalGreymon is fine,
but we can't have him evolving into SkullGreymon.
So we have him start over from Koromon.
What? Yeah, whatever, let's go with that.
The Star Plasma Vessel's location has been leaked.
Two groups are after the young girl's life as we speak.
One is the Curse User Group Q,
which seeks to upend jujutsu society
by having Master Tengen lose all reason.
The other is the Star Religious Group
that worships Master Tengen,
known as the Time Vessel Association.
Master Tengen will assimilate the Star Plasma Vessel
during the full moon in two days.
You are to protect the girl until then
and ensure that she reaches Master Tengen!
If you mess this up, the effects will ripple throughout even normal society!
Don't forget that!
Real talk, though.
I kinda get why Curse User Group Q is after her,
but why would this
Star Religious Group wanna kill the brat?
What they worship is the pure form of Master Tengen.
Allowing the Star Plasma Vessel—in their minds,
an impurity—to blend into him is simply unacceptable.
The Star Religious Group
is an organization of non-sorcerers.
I don't think we need to worry about them.
The ones to be wary of are Q.
Well, I'm sure it'll be fine.
We're the strongest, after all.
That's why Master Tengen asked for us specifically, right?
What is it?
You know, Satoru,
I've been wanting to tell you this for a while.
You should be more mindful of the way you talk.
Say what?!
Especially when you're addressing your superiors.
We might end up meeting Master Tengen.
You should be more polite and humble.
You'd scare your juniors less, too.
Hah!
Screw that!
Come on, Satoru.
Never mind.
We'll discuss it later.
Coming.
Still alive?
I am, at least.
Would it be our fault if the brat died from that?
Don't blame me.
If you must hate someone, hate Tengen.
Wha—
Could you please try not to make a scene?
We got chewed out for it just this morning.
This girl is the Star Plasma Vessel?
I know that uniform.
You're sorcerers from Jujutsu Tech.
Hand over the brat.
Or I'll kill you.
Can't hear you.
Come a little closer, will you?
Man, you barely made it.
Impressive.
You're Gojo Satoru, right?
You're famous.
I hear you're strong.
Let me confirm if the rumors are true.
I'm down for that, but let's set a rule.
What rule?
I don't wanna get yelled at for going overboard.
So if you start bawling and apologizing, I won't kill you.
That's the rule.
Cocky bastard.
And so it begins.
The Star Religious Group
doesn't have the power to fight sorcerers.
But they can pay very well.
That I guarantee.
How about it, Zenin?
Want to get in on the Star Plasma Vessel assassination?
It's not Zenin anymore.
I took my wife's name.
I go by Fushiguro now.
Alright, count me in.
You know how sometimes these
random words get stuck in your head?
Like, Privatization of Reclaimed Lands Act?
Exactly! Or like, Corporate Governance!
Please look forward to the next episode,
Hidden Inventory, Part 2!
You tell us one too, Shoko.
Clippity-Cloppity Carnival.
Whoa!