Please!
Please listen to me!
I was wrong!
I'm sorry!
I'm really sorry!
Let's kiss!
Huh?!
I'll pull out of this job!
I'll quit being a curse user, too!
Let's kiss!
C'mon, kiss!
Of course I'll quit Q, too!
I know! I'll go back to the countryside and farm rice!
I know you can hear me!
Like a curse user could cut it as a farmer.
You can hear me!
Damn student acting all condescending!
Lick, lick.
But Bayer is here, too!
He's Q's strongest combatant!
He'll take care of you and these things!
Hey.
Is this your "Bayer"?
Huh?
That's him.
And all the boats are off at once.
From the inside, we have Numbers 1, 2, 4, 5, 3, and 6 starting the race.
They're off with a beautiful straight shot.
And just what are you doing after suddenly disappearing on me?
Getting more money.
I've never seen you win once.
What about your job?
Oh, give it a rest.
You're talking like I'm unemployed.
Because you are.
As a mediator, it's my duty to report how the job's going to the client.
I'm up against the Gojo clan's kid.
I wouldn't be able to do anything if I just popped up in front of him.
I have to wear him down using some idiots first.
You go do your own damn job.
Already did, dumbass.
What were you thinking, letting go of the entire deposit?
I told you, wearing him down.
Don't you worry. All that money will come back to me.
Just like with this race.
Number 6, Hateno, crosses the line first!
Number 1, Doguchi, finishes next!
Following them in third is Number 2, Matsuda.
In fourth is Number 4, Nakaoka.
Tsk.
In fifth is Number 3, Tanaka.
You're not cut out for making easy money.
In sixth is Number 5, Okazaki, finishing last!
Number 6, Hateno, has given us an amazing comeback to watch in his first race!
I'm counting on you, Sorcerer Killer.
That was our third race of the day.
Oh, right.
How's Megumi doing?
Who's that?
Should we get her to a doctor?
I wish I could use reverse cursed energy like Shoko.
Yeah, that's impossible.
I can't understand a word she says about it.
You go "fwoo," then "hyoi."
Fwoo, hyoi. Get it?
You've got no sense for this.
You're awake.
You scum!
If you want to kill me, you'll be the one to die first!
Riko, calm down.
We're not with the group that attacked you.
Liar!
You have the face of a liar!
Your bangs are weird, too!
This is disrespectful!
P-Please stop it!
Kuroi!
Young lady, these men are our allies.
Kuroi, what are you riding on?
This is thanks to Bangs Guy's technique.
Could you please not call me that?
It's Curse Manipulation.
As the name suggests, I can absorb and manipulate cursed spirits.
This brat is more aggressive than I expected.
I was trying to figure out how to be considerate,
thinking she'd be more sentimental about the assimilation thing.
Hmph!
A commoner's way of thinking!
Huh?!
Listen up!
Master Tengen is me, and I am Master Tengen!
Some might mistake assimilation for death, as you do,
but there's a big difference!
I might become Master Tengen through the assimilation,
but Master Tengen will also become me!
My will! My heart!
My soul will continue to live on after the assimilation!
You changed your home screen?
To Inoue Waka.
Listen to me!
I bet you don't have many friends if you talk like that.
We won't have to feel bad sending you off.
I talk normally at school!
School!
Kuroi, what time is it?!
It's not yet noon. But I think going to school—
Be quiet!
I said I'm going, and I'm going!
Huh?!
Surely it'd be safer to head back to Jujutsu Tech at once!
As much as I want to do that, this is an order from Master Tengen.
He said to fulfill all of Amanai Riko's demands.
Tsk.
Lax upbringing at its finest.
Don't be like that, Satoru.
Despite what she may say,
after the assimilation, she'll spend her whole life as Master Tengen
in the deepest floor of Jujutsu Tech, as the foundation of all barriers.
She won't be able to see her friends, family, or anyone precious to her ever again.
Riko!
Our next class is in a different room.
Okay!
Let her do what she wants.
That's part of our mission.
Riko-sama has no family.
They were in an accident when she was little.
I've taken care of her ever since then.
So I want her to at least have what time she can with her friends.
So you're her family, then.
Yes.
Suguru.
How're the cursed spirits you sent to watch over her?
I just wish I could share my senses with them like Mei does.
Even so, they'll let us know as soon as anything unusual happens.
Satoru.
Hurry to Riko's side.
Huh?
Two have been exorcised.
Who will be the ace of the next generation?
This will be an important match to help us find out.
Number 6's final position is finally starting to solidify.
Now, the fifth race, the one all eyes are focused on, is about to begin.
Where's Amanai?!
She has music this period,
so either the music room or the chapel.
Chapel?!
It changes depending on what the music teacher wants.
Also, this is a missionary school.
Satoru, you take the chapel.
Kuroi, take the music room.
I'll take the two unknowns.
Roger that.
I told you not to follow me!
What if my friends see you?!
I'm sorry.
I even told her to text us when she was on the move.
This is why I told that brat to stay within eyeshot so we could protect her!
And they're off.
Numbers 1 and 2 make a good start, favoring the inside.
Number 3 trails a bit behind.
What?
Taking the lead at the first mark of the first lap is Number 2, Yamazaki.
They didn't go back to Jujutsu Tech?
Lucky me.
Behind him is Number 1, Masaki.
They're followed by Number 3, Kawano.
Now the ones drawn to the bounty will be reasonable fools instead of just fools.
Then comes Number 4, Nomiya, Number 5, Mifune, and in last is Number 6, Funegi.
Are you sure?
About what?
The bounty is the thirty-million deposit that the Star Religious Group paid you.
If they kill the Star Plasma Vessel, the deposit is gone,
and worst-case, you might not get the full reward, either.
They might start saying they could have posted
a bounty from the start instead of hiring you.
Gojo Satoru is with the girl.
He's the first in several centuries to possess both
the Six Eyes and the Limitless technique.
No one can kill the Star Plasma Vessel as long as he's nearby.
Not even you?
Number 3, Kawano, is making a rushing comeback!
He's pulled into first place!
Who knows?
He's managed to take the lead twice now.
For now, we'll leave the bounty up for another 47 hours,
This race has been filled with ups and downs.
Can Number 3, Kawano, defend his position at the top?
and let the fools wear down Gojo and the sorcerers with him.
The race is now entering its third lap.
Hey!
Hold it right there!
Nah, never mind.
They won't be able to kill the Star Plasma Vessel, of course,
so they're working for free.
It's a good thing you put that time limit on it.
The curse users are quickly flocking to them.
That's not the only reason.
Eh?
Just talking to myself.
What?!
Number 3, Kawano, just lost his balance, and Number 2, Yamazaki, is passing him!
Number 3 has drifted far to the outside,
I'll head out soon enough.
Looks like things are developing faster than I expected.
but he's righted his boat and is chasing after them!
But there is now a considerable gap between them!
Make sure you get that thirty million back for me.
Number 2, Yamazaki, crosses the goal first!
Number 5, Mifune, crosses next.
Don't be ridiculous.
This wasn't your average anonymous message board.
Number 1, Masaki, crosses next, followed by Number 3, Kawano.
Following them is Number 4, Nomiya, and last is Number 6, Funegi.
There are posting fees, handling fees, and—
Signal's dropping.
Hey!
That bastard.
Are the unknowns remnants of Q?
This will be a little troublesome if they've been sent by the Star Religious Group.
That uniform...
As soon as he saw the Jujutsu Tech uniform, he anticipated a fight against
multiple opponents and set shikigami in front of and behind him.
He's experienced.
No catalyst?!
Their cursed energy is different from the sorcerer's, too.
It couldn't be...
Curse Manipulation?!
Correct.
Living a long life has its perks, I see.
Nah, it's not worth living too long, you know.
It costs money just to stay alive.
His cursed technique is stronger than mine.
However, he thinks like a typical shikigami user.
Add his youth on top of that,
and I can tell exactly what he's thinking.
I knew it.
Types like him never step forward themselves.
Close combat is his weakness!
Plus, he thinks a shikigami user like me would never get close to him.
He's someone who hates close combat, and he isn't wary of it.
No one is easier to kill.
Looks like you're thinking up lots of plans,
but there's no point.
What?!
Those first two were to prevent me from anticipating this?!
Now, that leaves one more.
You're mine!
Tasuke? Is that you, Tasuke?
My parents used all their time and money on my well-behaved little brother.
They thought I was creepy because I could see the unseen.
But Tasuke was my one and only friend, who interacted with me without such fear.
It's been a long time.
Has it been over 50 years already?
Since the day you died—
I see now!
My life flashed before my eyes!
You lured me in!
Well, yeah.
You were itching to get in close that whole time, right?
Those with a set means of victory
will easily jump on the chance when you give them that opening.
More importantly, are you with Q?
Or the Star Religious Group?
Amanai!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wha...
What?!
Riko, you have a boyfriend?!
No! He's a cousin! Just a cousin!
You're a smooth operator.
I told you, he's not!
A high schooler?! He's so tall!
Hey, mister!
Take off your sunglasses!
Squee! He's so hot!
Such long lashes!
Hey.
Why are your eyes blue?
Could you pose for me?
Hey! Quit getting carried away!
All right, everyone! Quiet down!
This is disgraceful!
You know you're curious about him, too, !
Yeah.
This is inappropriate.
Even if you are a relative, you can't just barge in.
Oh, you'll have to forgive me. It was an emergency.
Also, here. My phone number.
Hey! That's against the rules!
Shut up! You don't get many chances to meet people as a teacher!
The same is true for us, too!
I can't believe you're into younger men! I've lost respect for you!
What?! You dissin' Hikaru Genji?!
What a lively school.
You idiot! I told you not to show yourself before my friends!
Curse users attacked. Figure out the rest.
I'm floating?!
We're heading to Jujutsu Tech now.
You don't want you friends to get caught up in this, do you?
Is that the thirty million?
The one with her is another sorcerer?
Her bodyguard, too, I bet.
What a sweet deal.
Thirty million for killing a kid who's not even a sorcerer.
Maybe I'll have eel tonight?
Food always tastes best after killing someone.
Are you from the Star Religious Group?
The people in Q wore even weirder outfits.
Are you a rookie?
If you're killing someone, do it without talking.
Too slow.
Don't you dare take anything from that girl.
I'll kill you.
What's this?
Well, aren't you strong?
Where's Riko?
She left the school with Gojo-sama.
Then we should head that way, too.
This has gotten a bit troublesome.
So that really was the thirty million earlier.
A shikigami?!
No, it's not quite the same as a shikigami.
Satoru.
There's a bounty of thirty million on Amanai's head?
Yeah. It was posted on an underground site for curse users.
Apparently, the time limit is 11 AM the day after tomorrow.
Now things make sense.
Two, three, four... They all look the same.
Are they shikigami?
Jeez... And jujutsu sorcerers are short-handed all year round.
If you want to change jobs, we'll welcome you, old man.
Nah, public employment ain't easy work, either.
Just hand over that brat and we'll be fine.
There's more! Five of them now!
What's so great about this brat?
What did you just do?
The shikigami isn't disappearing!
Which is the real one?!
They're not shikigami.
They're clones.
And each one is the real one.
The hell is this?!
Infinity.
It's Achilles and the Tortoise.
Huh?!
It's important to study, you know.
Yours is a cloning technique that allows a maximum of five, including the original.
And you're always free to decide which of the clones is the main body, right?
So if your main body is in danger,
you make a safe clone the main body.
That's a nice technique you have there.
I don't understand why you're so weak.
Are you unable to produce a clone for a while after it's destroyed?
How do you know what my technique is?
Unfortunately for you,
I have good eyes.
You see, my technique
is like a convergent series of infinite numbers.
Anything that approaches me grows slower and slower,
and ultimately, it fails to ever reach me.
When I amplify my Limitless technique,
I get what you might call a negative natural number.
It basically creates a single imaginary apple.
Doing so causes everything around to get sucked into that space, like you saw.
Though it's surprisingly inconvenient.
I can't create too large a reaction near myself,
and if I start worrying about the vectors, too,
controlling the cursed energy becomes a real pain.
Basically, it's super exhausting.
But that's all just the proper operation of the technique.
Protect your head.
This next one is the divergence of infinity.
My reverse cursed technique,
Red!
I failed!
I really thought I could do it that time.
Is this guy for real?
It's from Kuroi.
Wh-What do we do?!
Kuroi has...
Kuroi has been...
I've always thought the voices of young people should be heard,
so I've voted in every election,
but now I'm debating how long it's actually okay to consider myself a young person.
Next time, "Hidden Inventory 3"!
Be sure to watch!
Exactly how old are you, Kuroi?
It's a sekwet!
Oh, how cute!