I'm still wondering why I have to be executed.
It's your fault!
I don't want to regret the way I lived!
But what are you going to do when someone you saved kills someone else in the future?
When you die, you should be surrounded by people.
It's been decided that you'll be secretly executed.
I've already decided how I'm going to die.
That would mean people cursed me and my mom with those hearts!
What is a proper death?
The value of life would become ambiguous...
I wouldn't even understand the importance of those I care about anymore.
And that scares me.
It's your fault!
When you die, you should be surrounded by people.
Help others.
Guess I can't afford to die now.
So I've never once regretted saving you.
We're accomplices.
I won't...
lose again.
Then I'm gonna win.
Apologize...
to my brothers in the afterlife!
You're a strong kid, so help others.
Are you ready to witness it, Itadori?
People die. There's no stopping that.
So I wanted them to at least have proper deaths.
Are you going to blame your grandfather when you're killed by a curse, too?
...and have lots of them watching over me when I die.
But tears were shed over the lives I ended tonight.
People are going to die because you live!
Malaysia...
Yeah...
Kuantan would be nice.
I'll build a home on a secluded beach.
I already have a mountain of books that I've bought and never touched.
I'll read through them page by page,
like I'm taking back all the time I've lost.
No.
Right now, I'm going to save Fushiguro...
And Maki?
What about Naobito?
What happened to those two?
I'm tired.
Exhausted, even.
Yeah, I'm exhausted.
I've already done enough.
You're here?
I've been here. The whole time.
Shall we chat for a bit?
You and I have gone at it a few times, after all.
Haibara, what was I even hoping to accomplish in the end?
I ran.
I ran away, and yet I came back over some vague reason like a job worth doing.
I can't.
That's wrong.
I can't, Haibara.
I can't say that.
It'll just become a curse upon him.
Nanamin...
I shouldn't.
I sh—
Itadori.
You take it from here.
Wha—
What the hell...
What the hell are you, Mahito?!
You don't have to shout! I can hear you!
Itadori Yuji!
Save me!
Soul Multiplicity!
Body Repel!
If only I'd used a little more force,
I could've stabbed through your face.
How can you possibly
toy with countless
people's lives over and over?!
Would you be satisfied if I counted each one off my fingers with a look of regret?
I'll start doing that with the next one.
I'll grant you a simple answer since you're such a simple guy.
Itadori Yuji.
Help me!
You are me.
Huh?!
Quit snapping at everything.
It's just a curse's nonsense, right?
However,
until you're willing to accept that,
you can't beat me.
On and on...
You talk a lot.
Those your dying words?
You take it from here.
Nanamin would never make the mistake of losing himself to anger.
Prove it.
You are...
I am...
...a jujutsu sorcerer.
Nice. Let's keep going.
Time for round two!
Too close!
If I pick the wrong moments to take risks, I'll die.
I guess I'll attack mostly with transfigured humans for a while.
Oh, how scary.
He has even more tricks than before.
A kid?!
Hey! Over here!
It's dangerous and full of monsters over there!
It's...
upstairs?!
Sorry.
There's no safe place in Shibuya right now, so get as far away as you—
Shit! That bastard!
Come on now.
Huh?
Are you sure your imagination isn't stunted?
Stop it!
Are you an idiot?
That all depends on you.
This is the most effective tool against Itadori's mental state.
Plus...
We have one more card for insurance.
Huh?!
What?!
Hey!
Yeah, drink, drink, drink them up!
Drink, drink, drink them up!
Drink away!
Yay!
I have plenty stocked up already,
so you can do whatever you want with the people on floor B5.
Okay, time to recommence the "Let's Kill Itadori" show!
Burp!
No!
Jogo.
Catch me if you can!
Wha—
I'll take the underground.
You wander around the surface.
Just come back when I call you.
I know. You don't have to say it.
I guess so.
Bye-bye!
Boing!
He got away.
Mahito!
Did you see that earlier?
That was crazy, right?
I was just wandering around that area not long ago, too.
Patch-face...
Was it you?
Are you the special-grade cursed spirit that's been messing with our idiot?
Well, jeez.
Am I famous?
Yeah.
I heard you ran with your tail between your legs.
I like you.
You seem worth killing.
I haven't had any good chances to shine today...
They said this thing's technique had something to do with souls,
and not to let its hands touch me, right?
...so I'll have to settle for exorcising a cowardly bug like you.
Recall it.
Recall the essence of cursed energy that you seized back then!
No control.
Hairpin.
Not bad.
But in general, that won't work on me.
Judging from what she said,
she must be close to that guy.
I'll drag this woman's corpse
before Itadori Yuji and break his soul!
Time for a personality test!
Can you more clearly recall the person you used to love
or the person you used to hate?
Results after the title!
Next time, Judgement, Part 2.
Dwelling on the past means you're an otaku!