Ultimate Mechamaru, Mode: Absolute
“Armored Puppet Ultimate Mechamaru Prototype 0”
17 years 1 month 29 days
16 Years
Episode 31
Evening Festival
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Shibuya Incident
9 Years 5 Months 6 Days
Today's Weather
November 1, Heisei 30 [Hokkaido] Sunny, Partly Cloudy [Aomori] Rain [Miyagi]
JUJUTSU KAISEN
20:14, Tokyo, Shibuya
Same Time, Tokyo Metro Shibuya Station
Exit #13 (Outside the Veil)
For Health Insurance, Choose
Team Nanami
Kento Nanami (Grade 1 Jujutsu Sorcerer)
Takuma Ino (Grade 2 Jujutsu Sorcerer) (Under Evaluation for Promotion)
Megumi Fushiguro (Grade 2 Jujutsu Sorcerer) (Under Evaluation for Promotion)
Same Time, Shibuya Mark City
Restaurant Avenue Entrance (Outside the Veil)
Team Zen'in
Naobito Zen'in (Special Grade 1 Jujutsu Sorcerer)
Maki Zen'in (Grade 4 Jujutsu Sorcerer) (Under Evaluation for Promotion)
Nobara Kugisaki (Grade 3 Jujutsu Sorcerer) (Under Evaluation for Promotion)
Same Time, JR Shibuya Station South Entrance (Outside the Veil)
Grade 1 Jujutsu Sorcerer (Tokyo Jujutsu High Second-year Teacher)
Atsuya Kusakabe
Team Kusakabe
Atsuya Kusakabe (Grade 1 Jujutsu Sorcerer)
Panda (Grade 2 Jujutsu Sorcerer) (Promotion Evaluation Postponed)
Same Time, Bunkamura Street
Dogenzaka 2-Chome East (Inside the Veil)
Wednesday, October 31
Connection Error
Unable to Connect to Network
20:31 Satoru Gojo Arrives
Next Episode
The Shibuya Incident