Oh, no!
You've done it now, Kugisaki.
This was Gojo's, right?
Between Ijichi, who left us in charge of this freshly cleaned shirt,
and me, who spilled coffee on it...
Who's more at fault?
You.
You pat it down, pat it down.
I'm working on it!
It kind of looks like a marimekko.
Don't take apparel so lightly.
Eh, I'm sure it's a cheap shirt, anyway.
Fushiguro, look up the brand on the tag.
A-After tax?
Before tax.
Is that even important?
We have no choice.
I'll put in 90,000.
You can each put in 80,000.
Huh?!
Morning!
Ijichi said you guys had my shirt?
What's the matter, Megumi?
Nothing.
Kugisaki...
I-I can't...
I'm thrilled!
By my own talent!
Ah, I really am...
I truly am...
a curse!
Black Flash!
I bet you just thought
this would be some pest extermination,
or like defeating evil spirits in a legend,
or something like that when you came here, right?!
You're naïve! You damn brat!
This is war!
It's not some fight to correct a mistake!
It's a clash of what we believe is right!
Of our own flimsy ideas of justice!
You are me, Itadori Yuji.
Just as I kill people without a second thought,
you save people without a second thought!
It's our instincts
versus the dignity gained by human reasoning!
This is a war to determine which of those will be left standing a century from now!
If you haven't even realized that yet,
how are you supposed to beat me?
Hey, Itadori Yuji.
Have you counted how many curses you've killed?
I bet not.
Me, neither!
I really couldn't care less about the number of humans I've killed.
Eventually, I'll forget all about you, too.
The bells of the Gion monastery in India
echo with the warning that all things are impermanent.
The blossoms of the sala trees teach us through their hues
that what flourishes must fade.
However!
We are the exception!
These people...
are alive, right?
It looks like Geto Suguru has already left with the Prison Realm.
No way!
Let's switch gears.
Our goal has changed from fighting to reclaim Gojo Satoru
to fighting to save our allies and shave away as much of the enemy forces as possible,
starting right now!
Let's hurry.
My brother should already be nearby.
He has a brother?
I could have sworn he was an only child.
What just happened?
A face with a scar!
Plus the way he switched places just now!
Is he the sorcerer who drove Hanami into a corner?!
Todo!
I finished treating that girl over there.
She's probably dead, though.
So please don't blame me later!
Enough prattle.
See to my brother, too.
Wake up, Brother!
Our battle has just begun!
Talk about ominous lines!
Todo...
I...
can't...
fight anymore!
It wasn't just Kugisaki...
Nanamin died, too.
Sukuna... killed so many.
So I have to save...
that many more people...
But I couldn't!
I'm just a murderer!
What I thought was my conviction
was just an excuse I made for myself!
I can't...
forgive myself anymore.
Speak up! I can't hear you!
Amazing!
Even when you know about it, it's still this disorienting?!
Brother...
A man as great as you shouldn't let yourself grow so small.
We are jujutsu sorcerers.
Me,
you,
Kugisaki,
Mr. Nanami,
and all of our allies are jujutsu sorcerers!
So long as we continue to live,
our dead comrades
have not truly been defeated!
This is not a matter of sins and punishments.
The moment we chose to live as jujutsu sorcerers,
our lives were no longer bound by such karma.
Attempting to find meaning in the deaths of the fallen
can, at times, defile the memories of those we've lost!
But even so!
What have they entrusted you with?
There's no need to find your answer to that now.
But until you do,
you cannot stop moving forward.
That is the one punishment imposed
on those who live as jujutsu sorcerers.
There's no need to tell my brother about that right now.
I've applied my technique to you.
Now, listen up, Itadori.
The wounds you have suffered so far will no longer worsen.
They are not healed,
but you'll stop losing blood, and it should take the edge off the pain.
But that only applies to your current wounds.
If you take another attack, you'll be further wounded,
and my technique won't apply to those.
Todo's little brother doesn't resemble him at all.
I gave the girl over there the same treatment.
She didn't have a pulse and wasn't breathing,
but it hadn't been very long.
The chance that she survives isn't zero.
I'm taking her with me and getting out of here.
I'm just saying the chance isn't zero!
Please don't get your hopes up too high!
Yeah...
Yeah!
Are you finished talking, topknot gorilla?
What's wrong?
You won't touch me?
He's skilled.
He's parrying me while also keeping distance from the nearly finished Itadori.
That's not all I've got.
He dodged it?
Bring on the switch!
This time, I'll adapt!
I'll hit him for sure!
I want to land that thing once more!
I can feel myself close to reaching it!
The true essence of my soul!
I'm sorry, Nanamin.
I was trying to take the easy way out.
I even used my sins as an excuse to run away.
Please take it from here.
Black Flash!
I'll make sure I take on your share of suffering, too, Nanamin.
Tsk! Half-dead boy!
Welcome back.
Yeah!
Matters should be settled already.
There's no point in going to Shibuya now.
Head back, Miwa.
Why only Todo and Nitta?
I reasoned there's a 99% chance that Todo won't die in Shibuya.
Same for Nitta if he accompanied Todo.
His technique would be useful, too—
And me?!
Am I useless?
The situation isn't even on that scale anymore.
It wasn't just you.
It was Mai, Kamo, Nishimiya, and Utahime, too.
I took steps to make sure you all were on a mission south of Kyoto on the 31st.
Why didn't you say anything to us?
Why didn't you ask us for help?
Aren't we friends?
Is it because...
I'm weak?
No. I'm the one who was weak.
I went about it the wrong way because I was weak,
and I couldn't even see that mistake through because I was weak.
There was this girl I loved.
And I didn't care what happened to the world
as long as I could be at her side and protect her.
Even if that girl didn't want me
to be the one to protect her.
Time's up, Miwa.
No!
Goodbye. Thank you—
Don't say goodbye!
Miwa.
Mechamaru!
Miwa!
Please find happiness.
Whatever shape it takes, as long as you're happy,
my wish has come true.
Mechamaru...
Utahime, what Mechamaru did...
Will go unquestioned.
The man is dead, after all.
He held us in awfully low regard, huh?
Right?
And this whole "Todo wouldn't die" crap?
Is he saying that we would die, then?
I'll murder whoever makes my cute junior cry.
He can switch positions with inanimate objects?!
He split apart!
Soul Multiplicity!
Body Repel!
Topknot Gorilla's soul is still at full strength,
but could I kill him with one touch in my current state?
Itadori's soul is down to about 10% left.
And my soul is down to 40%.
Having my double crushed
and eating Itadori's rush of Black Flashes shaved away an awful lot.
And that's all thanks to that woman.
She was a nobody, but she still left her damn mark behind.
I'll start by eliminating this annoying switcher first!
Brother!
If you're satisfied with staying on that level,
you and I won't stay best friends.
This cursed spirit is already landing Black Flash, too...
I'm the one being left behind right now.
You've grown strong, Brother.
Are you satisfied with that,
Aoi Todo?!
Are you planning to leave your brother alone once again,
Tan-taka-tan!
Black Flash!
It doesn't matter how powerful your attack is,
or if you throw out a Black Flash.
Your attacks don't affect my soul, so they're pointless.
However, with that, all three of them were now...
Smooch!
...drawing out 120% of their latent potential.
Soul Multiplicity!
Body Repel!
An omnidirectional attack that makes switching pointless!
He's getting into high gear!
Let's kick it up a notch, Itadori!
This will be the last time
you and I curse each other!
They say a hero always arrives late,
but everyone understands that those who worked hard
and held out are heroes, too, right?
Next time, Metamorphosis.
Don't forget to grab your delay certificate!