Before the good in me crumbles away entirely
I should have told you everything
In a life descending and dissolving into the night
My tangled emotions flicker like a dim light
"That's just how it is, there's no other way"
Sure, I understand all that
But something's still missing
Why does it all feel so meaningless?
That something I thought could be anywhere
I realized can be found only here
In our dumb quarrels and conversations
Or when you show me that blush on your face
And so the moon is dark tonight
Head feels light
Another day I remain unbroken
What was I looking for, again?
My love's wavering
Gotta keep it hidden
And so the moon is dark tonight
Head feels light
Can't get outta bed today
Lemme sleep and sleep 'till the next day
Is this loneliness? Am I crying? So annoying
My already hazy memories are dying
Can't even recall last night
And so the moon is dark tonight
Distorts the light
Where are we going tomorrow?