Hidden Inventory / Premature Death
The blue spring of youth stretches out as far as the eye can see
Not a single cloud between us and this breathtaking view
The cicadas' song reverberates off the road
Drowning out your deafening silence
These colors will fade away someday
Even if I etch your scent into my memory
Into the depths of eternity they'll drown
Even today, our youth is shining blue
Even today, our blue shines through
All my wishes and prayers for you
They get close only to get farther
Like whispers of a love untold
Amidst hues of a fleeting summer streaming down my face
Stuck at the back of my throat are words that are a curse to you
"You know we'll meet again, right?"
As my voice gives out on me
Throughout Heaven and Earth
I alone am the honored one
Like grains of stars in the endless galaxy
Throughout Heaven and Earth
I alone am the honored one
Like grains of stars in the endless galaxy
Throughout Heaven and Earth
I alone am the honored one
Slipping through the gaps between my fingers
Throughout Heaven and Earth
I alone am the honored one
Slipping through the gaps between my fingers
Throughout Heaven and Earth
I alone am the honored one