You are my special
Shibuya Incident
Let's keep dancing until our dying breath
Tokyo's the heart of all the action
Let's keep struggling until there's nothing left
Show me just how wild you can get
I love you baby
Let's keep singing
No matter how absurd it is
No matter how out of place
Every move you make
Lights a fire in my heart
Got me losing control 'cause you are my special
Won't you mess me up, set the night on fire?
Devour everything to your heart's content
After an eternity in this maze, we meet at last
To the point it makes me faint, you are my special
World goes round and round, with or without answers
No! No! No need to bring along your sanity
After an eternity in this maze, we meet at last
No matter what anyone says, you are my special
We're special